<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Dragonlance]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/</link><image><url>https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Dragonlance</title><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/</link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 23:47:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 23:47:33 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator></dc:creator><item><title><![CDATA[10. June 1st, 2024 Connecting Threads]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>Krynn's Vanguard had rested up in Ker-Manth and went out to investigate the path in the cave that they hadn't explored before. They wound up coming up on a dead-end of a constructed hallway within the cave system. Searching for a hidden entrance, Tehv'in found his hand go through a wall. Upon walking through, he found himself in a city of Duergars and Intellect Devourers. <br>One of the Duergars noticed the party and asked Valphire if he had brought 'food for the masters'. Investigating who these 'masters' were, the party let the duergar lead them to their leader, a Matron Mother Drow. She had the party taken into captivity, save for Valphire and lightly questioned her being slightly suspicious. <br>Thoughout the day, Valphire found their way into the place where the party was being kept, and helped them escape along with their equipment behind a door further down the natural cave they were being held in. When they retrieved their gear, another creature asked them what they were doing, and after a short exchange with the Mind Flayer that came up behind them, they stated "The Psionic Maw has no need for you." And with a flash of light, the party found themselves on top of a hill, about a 10 minute walk from the village.<br>Upon returning, Krynn's Vanguard relayed what they saw to the village elders and to Lady Rhea when they returned to the monastery, and began preparations to guard the Holy Mausoleum for the Rite of Rising.]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/session-notes/10.-june-1st,-2024-connecting-threads.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/10. June 1st, 2024 Connecting Threads.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 15:52:28 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>