<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Dragonlance]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/</link><image><url>https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Dragonlance</title><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/</link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 01:53:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 01:53:58 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[Relgoth]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Relgoth is the capital city of the province of Vingaard on the Plains of Solamnia in Solamnia. The city is located along the <a data-href="Knight's High Road" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/locations/solamnia-and-the-northern-wastes/plains-of-solamnia/geography/knight's-high-road.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Knight's High Road</a>, northwest of <a data-href="Delgaard" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/locations/solamnia-and-the-northern-wastes/plains-of-solamnia/cities/delgaard.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Delgaard</a> and southeast of <a data-href="Ryn" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/locations/solamnia-and-the-northern-wastes/plains-of-solamnia/cities/ryn.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Ryn</a> along a branch of the Vingaard River. Relgoth is located in a dry, bowl-shaped valley, where the city is about a mile away from the crest of the valley. The city is led by the Lord of Relgoth.<br><br><br>Following the War of the Lance, construction was underway to build the New City District in Relgoth, after a population boom due to the discovery of minerals. Building continued until the Summer of Chaos, when shadow wights attacked the city. The New City District was left deserted, and even when the Knights of Takhisis took over control of the city; they left this district to the orphans, elderly and infirm residents of Relgoth.<br><br>In the city of Relgoth, no area is older than the Noble Quarter. The original district of the city, it was once home to only the nobles, wealthy merchants and privileged of Relgoth. However following the takeover of Relgoth by the Knights of Takhisis in the Age of Mortals, the Noble Quarter now houses all able-bodied folk who still remain within the city walls.<br><br>The Old City District was the largest district in the city of Relgoth, and prior to the War of Lance and building of the New City district, it comprised almost the entirety of the city. All the shops and a good deal of the residences were located here, although following the arrival of the Knights of Takhisis during the Age of Mortals, it is now their residence. The few residents of Relgoth who remain in this district serve as slaves to the knights and their mercenaries.<br><br><br>The Bastion of Darkness was a huge black stronghold located in Old City District in the city of Relgoth. Resembling an anthill of sorts, the walls are made of black sand and it once housed the slave overseer of the city. Small openings are spread around the walls of the fortress, and one large maw is located at ground level, serving as the primary entrance. Three huge towers rose from the stronghold, each standing thirty feet high.<br>The Bastion of Darkness was surrounded by a scorpion filled moat and was decimated by the mage Palin Majere during the early part of the Age of Mortals. The residents of Relgoth are being forced to now clean the black sand of the fortress from the city at the behest of the Knights of Takhisis.<br><br>Located on a low hill between the Noble Quarter and the Old City is Castle Rel. The fortress serves as a residence for the rulers of the city of Relgoth.<br><br>A vast wall surrounds the city of Relgoth making it near impenetrable. The only entrances into the city and between districts are via the great gates of Relgoth. One pair of gates stands at the entrance to the New City District, and is the only entrance into the city itself. Another pair serves as the gateway from the New City to the Old City District, whilst another leads from Old City to the Noble Quarter, and a final set leads from the Noble Quarter to Castle Rel.<br><br>In 250 PC, having suffered from the hands of brigands and bandits, the Lord of Relgoth proposed to build a great wall around his city, to protect it from enemies. Whilst the lord himself died during the construction, rumors were rife that his spirit merged with the wall to make it stronger and completely impenetrable. The walls stood firm against all attacks made against it, until the Summer of Chaos, when shadow wights decimated Relgoth and it's buildings. Later on, the Walls of Relgoth were rebuilt in beautiful white stonery with thier surface being almost completely smooth. The stark contrast of the stonework against the plains and it's heavy fortification earned the city the nickname of The Silver Maiden. Ever since these walls were built, Relgoth has repelled every single attack no matter how large. No one has managed to make it to the inner city...not even once.<br><br><br>Knight's Road is the only major road that leads from the outside into the city of Relgoth. The road leads from The Gates of Relgoth and runs in a winding fashion through the New City, Old City, Noble Quarter and ends at the entrance to Castle Rel.<br><br>Vingaard Road is a major highway that runs between the cities of Relgoth and Vingaard. The road begins in Relgoth as an offshoot from Knight's Road and leads eastward out of the city and across the Solamnic Plains all the way to Vingaard. The road is used regularly for merchant caravans and all manner of travelers through the realm of Solamnia.]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/locations/solamnia-and-the-northern-wastes/plains-of-solamnia/cities/relgoth.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Locations/Solamnia and the Northern Wastes/Plains of Solamnia/Cities/Relgoth.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 01:34:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cornelia Arnim]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Cornelia.jpg" src="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/cornelia.jpg"><br>
Personality Traits: Manipulative, intelligent, and ambitious. Cornelia is cunning and knows how to play her cards right.<br>Ideals: Power and control. She seeks to expand her influence and control over Palanthas.<br>Bonds: Her loyalty lies with the forces manipulating Solamnia from behind the scenes, particularly Those Who Slither in the Dark.<br>Flaws: Ruthless and deceitful. Cornelia is willing to betray anyone to achieve her goals.<br>Backstory: Cornelia is a skilled mage who became the court mage of Palanthas. Her true allegiance, however, is to Those Who Slither in the Dark. She played a significant role in the political turmoil in Solamnia, orchestrating the Tragedy of Tarnis and manipulating key figures to ensure her plans came to fruition. By the beginning of the war phase, she has solidified her control over Palanthas.<br>Status: Alive]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/cornelia-arnim.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NPCs/Holy Kingdom of Solamnia/Cornelia Arnim.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 22:56:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/cornelia.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/cornelia.jpg"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Felix Hugo Fraldarius]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Felix.png" src="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/felix.png"><br>
Personality Traits: Blunt, independent, and fiercely competitive. Felix speaks his mind and values strength above all else.<br>Ideals: Strength and personal freedom. He despises weakness and seeks to become the strongest warrior.<br>Bonds: Complex relationship with his family, particularly his father <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Holy Kingdom of Solamnia/Rodrigue Achille Fraldarius.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/rodrigue-achille-fraldarius.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Rodrigue</a> and his deceased brother Glenn. Close friends with <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Holy Kingdom of Solamnia/Dimitri Alexandre Blaiddyd.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/dimitri-alexandre-blaiddyd.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dimitri</a> and <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Holy Kingdom of Solamnia/Sylvain Jose Gautier.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/sylvain-jose-gautier.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Sylvain</a>.<br>Flaws: Aloof and abrasive. Felix often pushes others away due to his harsh demeanor and obsession with strength.<br>Backstory: Felix is the second son of Duke Rodrigue Fraldarius. After his brother Glenn died in the Tragedy of Tarnis, Felix became disillusioned with the ideals of knighthood and grew resentful of the chivalric code. He joined the Blue Lions at Garreg Mach Monastery, often clashing with his childhood friends, particularly Dimitri, due to their differing views on strength and leadership.<br>Status: Deceased]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/felix-hugo-fraldarius.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NPCs/Holy Kingdom of Solamnia/Felix Hugo Fraldarius.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 01:40:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/felix.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/felix.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gwendal Roche]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Gwendal.jpg" src="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/gwendal.jpg"><br>
Personality Traits: Stern, dutiful, and disciplined. Gwendal is a seasoned warrior with a no-nonsense attitude.<br>Ideals: Duty and honor. He is committed to serving his country and upholding its traditions.<br>Bonds: Loyal to Cornelia and his subordinates, though his true feelings about Cornelia's actions are complicated.<br>Flaws: Rigid and inflexible. He has difficulty adapting to changing circumstances and questioning orders.<br>Backstory: Gwendal is a general in the Kingdom of Solamnia and a loyal follower of Cornelia. He has served the kingdom faithfully for many years and is known for his stern demeanor and strict adherence to duty. Despite his loyalty, he harbors doubts about some of Cornelia's actions but remains committed to his role as a protector of the kingdom.<br>Status: Alive]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/gwendal-roche.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NPCs/Holy Kingdom of Solamnia/Gwendal Roche.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 22:56:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/gwendal.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/gwendal.jpg"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Holy Kingdom of Solamnia]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br><br><br>]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NPCs/Holy Kingdom of Solamnia/Holy Kingdom of Solamnia.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 01:53:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ingrid Brandl Galatea]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Ingrid.png" src="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/ingrid.png"><br>
Personality Traits: Noble, responsible, and courageous. Ingrid embodies the ideals of knighthood.<br>Ideals: Honor and chivalry. She strives to be a model knight and protect her homeland.<br>Bonds: Close friends with <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Holy Kingdom of Solamnia/Felix Hugo Fraldarius.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/felix-hugo-fraldarius.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Felix</a>, <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Holy Kingdom of Solamnia/Sylvain Jose Gautier.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/sylvain-jose-gautier.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Sylvain</a>, and <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Holy Kingdom of Solamnia/Dimitri Alexandre Blaiddyd.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/dimitri-alexandre-blaiddyd.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dimitri</a>. She is also deeply committed to her family's well-being. She formed these bonds after the death of her fiancée, Glenn, Felix's brother, during the Tragedy of Tarnis.<br>Flaws: Overly idealistic and sometimes naive about the realities of war and politics. She can be self-sacrificial to a fault.<br>Backstory: Ingrid is the daughter of Count Galatea and has always dreamed of becoming a knight. She attended Garreg Mach Monastery as a member of the Blue Lions, seeking to uphold the ideals of knighthood and bring honor to her family. Despite the financial struggles of House Galatea, Ingrid remains committed to her goal of becoming a true knight and protecting those she cares about.<br>Status: Alive]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/ingrid-brandl-galatea.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NPCs/Holy Kingdom of Solamnia/Ingrid Brandl Galatea.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 01:40:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/ingrid.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/ingrid.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rodrigue Achille Fraldarius]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Rodrigue.jpg" src="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/rodrigue.jpg"><br>
Personality Traits: Noble, steadfast, and honorable. Rodrigue is a paragon of chivalry and leadership.<br>Ideals: Duty and leadership. He believes in the responsibility of the nobility to lead and protect their people.<br>Bonds: Deeply cares for his son, <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Holy Kingdom of Solamnia/Felix Hugo Fraldarius.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/felix-hugo-fraldarius.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Felix</a>, and mourns the loss of his eldest son, Glenn. He is also loyal to <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Holy Kingdom of Solamnia/Dimitri Alexandre Blaiddyd.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/dimitri-alexandre-blaiddyd.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Prince Dimitri</a> and the Kingdom of Solamnia.<br>Flaws: Traditional and sometimes rigid in his views. He struggles to understand Felix's rebellious nature.<br>Backstory: Rodrigue is the head of House Fraldarius and a trusted ally of the royal family of Solamnia After the death of his son Glenn in the Tragedy of Tarnis, Rodrigue became more dedicated to his duties, though his relationship with his surviving son, Felix, became strained. He continues to support Prince Dimitri and the kingdom, upholding the ideals of knighthood and leadership.<br>Status: Deceased]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/rodrigue-achille-fraldarius.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NPCs/Holy Kingdom of Solamnia/Rodrigue Achille Fraldarius.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 01:40:25 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/rodrigue.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/rodrigue.jpg"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[24. November 2nd, 2024 Siege of Relgoth]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>After capturing Qualinost and talking with <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Abanasinian Empire/Volkhard Von Arundel.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/abanasinian-empire/volkhard-von-arundel.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Lord Arundel</a>, the party spent a few days in Qualinost gathering supplies and resting as they awaited for <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Abanasinian Empire/Count Leopold Von Bergliez.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/abanasinian-empire/count-leopold-von-bergliez.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Count Bergliez</a> to arrive. After Edelgard spoke with him and they set out, Edelgard revealed her plan to them. They had announced that they were going straight for the Kingdom capital, <a data-href="Palanthas" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/locations/solamnia-and-the-northern-wastes/palanthas/palanthas.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Palanthas</a>. The majority of their army was, whereas the most elite of their force, along with the Black Eagles and Krynn's Vanguard would be heading to <a data-href="Relgoth" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/locations/solamnia-and-the-northern-wastes/plains-of-solamnia/cities/relgoth.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Relgoth</a>, a fortress city near the front lines. <br>After scouting and some reports, it was apparent that Relgoth housed a number of Kingdom generals. Among them were; <a data-href="Cornelia Arnim" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/cornelia-arnim.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Cornelia Arnim</a>, a mage of the royal court; <a data-href="Ingrid Brandl Galatea" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/ingrid-brandl-galatea.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Ingrid Brandl Galatea</a>, a noble who was once a student of the Officer's Academy at Garreg Mach Monastery in the Blue Lions house and friend of <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Holy Kingdom of Solamnia/Dimitri Alexandre Blaiddyd.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/dimitri-alexandre-blaiddyd.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dimitri</a>; <a data-href="Gwendal Roche" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/gwendal-roche.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Gwendal Roche</a>, a renown knight of House Rowe known as the Grey Lion; <a data-href="Felix Hugo Fraldarius" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/felix-hugo-fraldarius.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Felix Hugo Fraldarius</a>, the eldest son of House Fraldarius, longtime friend of Dimitri, and former student of the Blue Lion house; and <a data-href="Rodrigue Achille Fraldarius" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/rodrigue-achille-fraldarius.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Rodrigue Achille Fraldarius</a>, the head of House Fraldarius, a Kingdom General, and Felix's father. During this investigation, Krynn's Vanguard learned that Cornelia has some 'sweet children' that she was planning to use to defend Relgoth.<br>After determining that the city had prepared it's forces, the Imperial Army laid siege to Relgoth, and began advancing into the city with their elite forces. While tough, Krynn's Vanguard, along with help from <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/The Black Eagles/Edelgard Von Hresvelg.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/the-black-eagles/edelgard-von-hresvelg.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Edelgard</a> and the Imperial Army, managed to break through the south and east entrances to the city. They quickly found that they may be in for more than they bargained for as Cornelia's aforementioned 'sweet children' were Titanus. A mechanical and magical construct that is heavily fortified and stands 90 feet tall. Although they had not attacked yet, they were something they would eventually have to deal with, at least get past without getting essentially removed from the fight.<br>While fighting mostly front line soldiers, Krynn's Vanguard and their main forces faced off with Rodrigue and Felix, felling both while being pelted with Cornelia's Ice Storm from long range. Meanwhile, the smaller eastern force broke through the guard a the gate and rushed to get as close to Cornelia as possible before finding out that the city was littered with traps, as they encountered more resistance in their path to victory.]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/session-notes/24.-november-2nd,-2024-siege-of-relgoth.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/24. November 2nd, 2024 Siege of Relgoth.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 01:51:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Session Notes]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br>]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/session-notes/session-notes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/Session Notes.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 01:27:04 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>