<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Dragonlance]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/</link><image><url>https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Dragonlance</title><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/</link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 21:08:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 21:08:33 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[Armantaro]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/krynns-vanguard/armantaro.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Krynns Vanguard/Armantaro.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 20:54:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ludwig Von Aegir]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Ludwig.jpg" src="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/ludwig.jpg"><br>
Personality Traits: Proud, authoritative, and pragmatic. Ludwig commands respect and carries himself with an air of nobility and power.<br>Ideals: Order and tradition. He believes in maintaining the established social order and upholding the traditions of the Abanasinian Empire.<br>Bonds: Loyal to the Empire and his family, particularly his son, <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/The Black Eagles/Ferdinand Von Aegir.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/the-black-eagles/ferdinand-von-aegir.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Ferdinand</a>. He has complex relationships with other noble houses.<br>Flaws: Stubborn and power-hungry. Ludwig is resistant to change and often prioritizes his own power and status over the needs of others.<br>Backstory: Ludwig von Aegir was the Prime Minister of the Abanasinian Empire and the head of House Aegir, one of the most powerful noble families in the Empire. Known for his political acumen and influence, Ludwig has played a key role in maintaining the stability and traditions of the Empire. He is a strict and demanding father to Ferdinand, expecting him to uphold the family's prestigious legacy. Ludwig's ambition and desire for power often put him at odds with other nobles and the ruling family, particularly after Edelgard ascends to the throne. His resistance to Edelgard's reforms and his own machinations for power create tension within the Empire, setting the stage for the conflicts to come. As of current, he is being held on very strict house arrest within the Empire and has been stripped of his duties as Prime Minister. None of this is known to the people of the Empire.]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/abanasinian-empire/ludwig-von-aegir.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NPCs/Abanasinian Empire/Ludwig Von Aegir.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 22:55:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/ludwig.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/ludwig.jpg"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Volkhard Von Arundel]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Arundel.jpg" src="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/arundel.jpg"><br>
Personality Traits: Calculating, manipulative, and ambitious. Volkhard is a master strategist who hides his true intentions behind a facade of nobility.<br>Ideals: Power and control. He seeks to consolidate power and influence within the Abanasinian Empire and beyond.<br>Bonds: Loyal only to himself and Those Who Slither in the Dark. He uses his connections and family ties to further his own agenda.<br>Flaws: Deceitful and untrustworthy. Volkhard is willing to betray anyone to achieve his goals and often underestimates the potential for resistance against his plans.<br>Backstory: Volkhard von Arundel, also known as <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Those Who Slither in the Dark/Thales.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/those-who-slither-in-the-dark/thales.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Thales</a>, is a high-ranking member of Those Who Slither in the Dark, a secretive and malevolent organization. As the uncle of Edelgard, he took on the role of regent after her father's health declined, effectively controlling the Abanasinian Empire from the shadows. He orchestrated numerous schemes to further his group's agenda, including the experiments on Edelgard and her siblings to implant them with multiple Marks. Under his guise as Volkhard, he appears to be a supportive and caring uncle, but his true motives are sinister. By the beginning of the war phase, his machinations have set the stage for widespread conflict, aiming to destabilize Ansalon and pave the way for his group's dominance.<br>Status: Alive]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/abanasinian-empire/volkhard-von-arundel.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NPCs/Abanasinian Empire/Volkhard Von Arundel.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 22:56:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/arundel.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/arundel.jpg"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hilda Valentine Goneril]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Hilda.png" src="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/hilda.png"><br>
Personality Traits: Lazy, carefree, and charming. Hilda prefers to avoid work whenever possible but is cheerful and sociable.<br>Ideals: Freedom and enjoyment. She values her freedom and dislikes being tied down by responsibilities.<br>Bonds: Close friends with <a class="internal-link" data-href="Marianne Von Edmund.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/qualinesti-alliance/marianne-von-edmund.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Marianne</a> and protective of her brother, Holst. She also develops a strong bond with <a class="internal-link" data-href="Claude Von Riegan.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/qualinesti-alliance/claude-von-riegan.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Claude</a>, obvious due to their romantic relationship.<br>Flaws: Indolent and sometimes irresponsible. She can be unreliable when it comes to serious matters.<br>Backstory: Hilda is the only daughter of House Goneril, a noble family in the Qualinesti Alliance. She attended Garreg Mach Monastery as a member of the Golden Deer. Despite her laziness, Hilda is a talented fighter and a loyal friend, often using her charm to get others to do her work. Her relationship with Claude and the other members of the Golden Deer helps her grow and take on more responsibility.<br>Status: Alive]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/qualinesti-alliance/hilda-valentine-goneril.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NPCs/Qualinesti Alliance/Hilda Valentine Goneril.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 14:24:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/hilda.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/hilda.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nader]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Nader.jpg" src="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/nader.jpg"><br>
Personality Traits: Bold, confident, and adventurous. Nader thrives in battle and has a larger-than-life presence, often boasting of his achievements.<br>Ideals: Strength and honor. Nader believes that power and courage in battle are the ultimate expressions of one's character, and he values a fair fight.<br>Bonds: Fiercely loyal to Almyra and its people, particularly to the king and the royal family. He respects Claude (Khalid) and sees him as a key figure in uniting Almyra with the rest of Fódlan.<br>Flaws: Overconfident and reckless. Nader often rushes headfirst into battle without fully considering the consequences, relying on his strength to carry him through.<br>Status: Alive]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/qualinesti-alliance/nader.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NPCs/Qualinesti Alliance/Nader.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 20:59:56 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/nader.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/nader.jpg"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Qualinesti Alliance]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br>]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/qualinesti-alliance/qualinesti-alliance.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NPCs/Qualinesti Alliance/Qualinesti Alliance.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 21:07:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[21. October 5th, 2024 Retribution]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>After losing his title and escaping from his house arrest, <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Abanasinian Empire/Ludwig Von Aegir.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/abanasinian-empire/ludwig-von-aegir.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Duke Aegir</a> fled to Ordelia territory within the Alliance, and subsequently gathers a quiet militia under his command.<br>Meanwhile, Krynn's Vanguard runs into <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Qualinesti Alliance/Lysithea Von Ordelia.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/qualinesti-alliance/lysithea-von-ordelia.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Lysithea</a>, who has learned about and grown tiresome of Duke Aegir's men running amok in her family's territory. It's made clear that Lysithea actually supports the Empire and has no intention of stopping them, even offering to help them get to Qualinost faster. After they quell the rioting militia, they discover that Duke Aegir has been slain. In return for helping run Duke Aegir's men out of her territory and saving the villagers, Lysithea fulfills her promise of showing them a passage that will lead them to <a data-href="Qualinost" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/locations/qualinesti/qualinost.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Qualinost</a>. After everything calms down, she uses some unknown magic to split the fountain in the city in half, which reveals a passage that leads underground. Taking them down, she intends to lead them to Qualinost.]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/session-notes/21.-october-5th,-2024-retribution.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/21. October 5th, 2024 Retribution.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 20:47:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[22. October 19th, 2024 The Master Tactician]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>With help from <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Qualinesti Alliance/Lysithea Von Ordelia.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/qualinesti-alliance/lysithea-von-ordelia.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Lysithea</a>, Krynn's Vanguard and a large portion of the Imperial Army made their way to <a data-href="Qualinost" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/locations/qualinesti/qualinost.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Qualinost</a> for the final assault against <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Qualinesti Alliance/Claude Von Riegan.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/qualinesti-alliance/claude-von-riegan.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Claude</a>. Qualinost was under orders that no one would enter or leave the city. Claude and his army set-up in a naval port and planned to play defense against the Imperial army. Among the soldiers included <a data-href="Armantaro" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/krynns-vanguard/armantaro.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Armantaro</a>, a relative of Claude, and <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Qualinesti Alliance/HIlda Valentine Goneril.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/qualinesti-alliance/hilda-valentine-goneril.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Hilda</a>.<br>The battle began and it was obvious that it was going to be hard fought, but the party was pretty assured to take care of business. But Claude is cunning, and he'd secured the support of the Silvanesti king, <a data-href="Nader" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/qualinesti-alliance/nader.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Nader</a>, who brought a small fleet and a contingent of soldiers with him, making the battle tougher.<br>After taking Armantaro down, <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/The Black Eagles/Edelgard Von Hresvelg.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/the-black-eagles/edelgard-von-hresvelg.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Edelgard</a> asked him to join them. She wasn't the nicest about it, but it was the heat of battle and she'd seen only a fraction of what he could do, but saw great potential and wanted him on her side. She got what she wanted.<br>The fight continued and the battle seemed to turn a bit as Krynn's Vanguard is being pushed to their limit. Will they be able to pull out the victory and topple the Alliance?]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/session-notes/22.-october-19th,-2024-the-master-tactician.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/22. October 19th, 2024 The Master Tactician.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 21:05:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Session Notes]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br>]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/session-notes/session-notes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/Session Notes.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 20:46:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Abanasinian Empire]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br>]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/abanasinian-empire/abanasinian-empire.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NPCs/Abanasinian Empire/Abanasinian Empire.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 23:38:10 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>