<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Dragonlance-Sync]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Dragonlance-Sync</title><link/></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:15:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:15:34 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[46. May 10th, 2025 The Kingdom of Dwarves]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>Krynn's Vanguard continued their venture through Thorbardin finding very little in their path. Any threats were quickly dispatched and didn't require much effort from the now very seasoned adventurers. It'd been about 12 years since the start of what is now dubbed The War of the Lance, but Krynn's Vanguard didn't really form until about 352 A.C. Even after 8 years (5 of which they disappeared for) and a number of roster changes, you'd be hard-pressed to find a group of adventurers as skilled and as synergistic as their group. Especially with two main combatants who hit like trucks in <a data-href="Orion" href="krynns-vanguard/orion.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Orion</a> and <a data-href="Arcadius" href="krynns-vanguard/arcadius.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Arcadius</a>. <a data-href="Orla" href="krynns-vanguard/orla.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Orla</a> adds more muscle and speed to the group while <a data-href="Armantaro" href="krynns-vanguard/armantaro.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Armantaro</a> provides ranged spell support and crowd control. <a data-href="Kyan Covverre" href="krynns-vanguard/kyan-covverre.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Kyan Covverre</a> and <a data-href="Big Bob" href="krynns-vanguard/big-bob.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Big Bob</a> bring up the support and utility part and much needed healing. A very well-rounded group indeed.<br>During their exploration they ran across a dead night hag with no visible injuries or obvious cause of death. They also, very smartly, avoided touching any of the walls covered in fungus or with any sort of ooze. They did find some fiendish sigils in one room that they marked with an 'X' on their growing map of the dwarven labyrinth. A longer tussle with some wraiths and specters gave them a rush of adrenaline but they were easily subdued after figuring out how to do actual damage to them. <br>One room they encountered some Bulezau that stood completely still and only said 'She's here'. Krynn's Vanguard concidered killing them, which is quite rude to do right in front of them but they didn't retaliate, and they left them alone. In the next room they encountered the Succubus they'd met earlier. It was odd to see her again but she didn't cause them any harm and left before the party could glean any information from her. The last room they cleared had them ambushed by a couple Black Puddings, more of a nuisance than an actual threat. Was the major threats only on the previous floor? Or were they deeper down...time would tell.]]></description><link>session-notes/46.-may-10th,-2025-the-kingdom-of-dwarves.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/46. May 10th, 2025 The Kingdom of Dwarves.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:15:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Session Notes]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br>]]></description><link>session-notes/session-notes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/Session Notes.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 15:55:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[East Road]]></title><description/></item></channel></rss>