<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Dragonlance-Sync]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Dragonlance-Sync</title><link/></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 22:46:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 22:46:04 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[49. June 14th, 2025 The Kingdom of Dwarves]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>It was a rough fight, but Krynn's Vanguard was able to defeat the pair of Balors. Moving forward they found a pair of dwarves that attacked them once they removed the makeshift barricade. The dwarves were unaware that they weren't demons. After all, it's been 3 months of scrounging, fighting, running, and whatever else they needed to do to survive the demon onslaught.<br>After some rude interactions...mainly <a data-href="Big Bob" href="krynns-vanguard/big-bob.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Big Bob</a>'s fault, the dwarves left. Krynn's Vanguard kept exploring through the floor with a few small scruffle's here and there before <a data-href="Kyan Covverre" href="krynns-vanguard/kyan-covverre.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Kyan Covverre</a> almost fell through the floor but managed to catch himself. Exploring the last room Krynn's Vanguard tied off a rope and went down the hole that was just big enough for them to get through. They found themselves descended into what was clearly a dungeon. Many cells and gnarly creatures here. In two cells they found dwarf zombies in one, and two Night Hags in another. Exploring the floor, Krynn's Vanguard found many a creature, mainly locked up, but mostly empty cells. They also ran into a Bodak and two Ghasts roaming around Should be a pretty easy cleanup.]]></description><link>session-notes/49.-june-14th,-2025-the-kingdom-of-dwarves.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/49. June 14th, 2025 The Kingdom of Dwarves.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 22:40:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[50. June 21st, 2025 The Kingdom of Dwarves]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>As expected, the undead were easy pickings for Krynn's Vanguard. Exploring further were more empty cells with a conglomeration of Fiends and Ooze creatures while they made their way to the East side of the floor. As they reached the end, they were suddenly attacked by two Citadel Spiders and a Cosmic Horror. It's unsure why the Cosmic Horror and the Citadel Spiders were working together, but Abberations are known to take over and command other creatures. Two Citadel Spiders wouldn't be too hard for a creature as rutheless as the Citadel Spiders.<br>After a long fight where both <a data-href="Orla" href="krynns-vanguard/orla.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Orla</a> and <a data-href="Arcadius" href="krynns-vanguard/arcadius.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Arcadius</a> got grappled and were Vortex Warpped to safety by <a data-href="Armantaro" href="krynns-vanguard/armantaro.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Armantaro</a>, the group whittled them down until they were defeated. Debating their next steps, they decided to take some time to think on whether they wanted to explore the rest of this floor and maybe clear out the floor they came from, or if they wanted to just rush through Floor 14 as they did know through some spectral scouting that if they rushed, they could make it to 15 without having to engage in combat. They were pretty low on resources, so taking some time made the most sense.]]></description><link>session-notes/50.-june-21st,-2025-the-kingdom-of-dwarves.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/50. June 21st, 2025 The Kingdom of Dwarves.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 22:44:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Session Notes]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br>]]></description><link>session-notes/session-notes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/Session Notes.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 22:45:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[East Road]]></title><description/></item></channel></rss>