<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Dragonlance-Sync]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Dragonlance-Sync</title><link/></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 18:33:01 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[28. December 14th, 2024 Clash at the Plains of Solamnia]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>Krynn's Vanguard continued the fight as it raged on. Aided by <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/The Black Eagles/Edelgard Von Hresvelg.md" href="npcs/the-black-eagles/edelgard-von-hresvelg.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Edelgard</a>, they took down <a data-href="Lady Rhea" href="npcs/the-church-of-seiros/lady-rhea.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Lady Rhea</a>, now known as Seiros, as she retreated with her forces, presumably to Palanthas for a final stand. With quick thinking from <a data-href="Armantaro" href="krynns-vanguard/armantaro.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Armantaro</a> and his Scatter spell, the group passed the river choke-point and made their way to the other side where <a data-href="Dedue Molinaro" href="npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/dedue-molinaro.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dedue Molinaro</a> used a mark stone to transform into a hideous beast, a Giant Demonic Beast.<br>After Edelgard was 'scattered' to right in front of <a data-href="Dimitri Alexandre Blaiddyd" href="npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/dimitri-alexandre-blaiddyd.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dimitri Alexandre Blaiddyd</a>, she wasted no time, using all of her might to dispatch him and end the fight. The rest of the Kingdom Army surrendered and were allowed to either join their ranks, or leave with their lives. Unfortunately, since they were already lost, both the Swordmaster who transformed and Dedue were dispatched.<br>After the battle and setting up camp at <a data-href="The High Clerist's Tower" href="locations/solamnia-and-the-northern-wastes/palanthas/the-high-clerist's-tower.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The High Clerist's Tower</a>, <a data-href="Arcadius" href="krynns-vanguard/arcadius.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Arcadius</a>, scouted around the site. He spotted a figure of ethereal blue flames wearing Solmanic Armor headed towards the tower. Upon closer inspection, this was one of The Foresworn that lived in <a data-href="Dargaard Keep" href="locations/solamnia-and-the-northern-wastes/nightlund/dargaard-keep.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dargaard Keep</a>, which was now under Krynn's Vanguard's governance. They had come to give Krynn's Vanguard their profits from the Keep and it's surrounding lands, 150 thousand gold pieces split between them.<br>Meanwhile, <a data-href="Orla" href="krynns-vanguard/orla.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Orla</a> tried, and failed, to find an accountant to help her set up an endowment with their wealth. <a data-href="Armantaro" href="krynns-vanguard/armantaro.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Armantaro</a> teleported back to <a data-href="Qualinost" href="locations/qualinesti/qualinost.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Qualinost</a> to check on the people there and find his family's accountant. The people there were doing well. Not as well as they were before the war, but well on their way to recovering from the war and seemed to be doing just fine, and will be doing better once the town is rebuilt and the economy starts to recover.<br>In the library of The High Clerist's Tower, Armantaro did some research and found some books that were of great importance. Some books mentioned <a data-href="Those Who Slither in the Dark" href="those-who-slither-in-the-dark.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Those Who Slither in the Dark</a>and some of their members. They mentioned an unheard of group known as <a data-href="The Abyssal Concord of Utter Chaos" href="the-abyssal-concord-of-utter-chaos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Abyssal Concord of Utter Chaos</a>, simply known as The Concord. They had a subsection in their hierarchy known as The Abyssal Council of Thirteen. Surprisingly, there was a plethora of information on this group and their motives.<br>One of the warplans that was considered was having the army go ahead of Krynn's Vanguard and The Black Eagles. After things started to heat up, they could use <a data-href="Kyan Covverre" href="krynns-vanguard/kyan-covverre.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Kyan Covverre</a>'s Word of Recall to teleport into the thick of things and be closer to their target, The Immaculate One. With <a data-href="Big Bob" href="krynns-vanguard/big-bob.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Big Bob</a> cooking up some delicious food, and the army ready to strike, it was time to invade Palanthas. ]]></description><link>session-notes/28.-december-14th,-2024-clash-at-the-plains-of-solamnia.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/28. December 14th, 2024 Clash at the Plains of Solamnia.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 18:32:43 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>