<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Dragonlance]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/</link><image><url>https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Dragonlance</title><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/</link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 07:42:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 07:42:30 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[20. September 28th, 2024 The Darken Wood]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>After arriving in <a data-href="Crossing" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/locations/abanasinia/crossing.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Crossing</a> and stocking up on potions and other equipment, Krynn's Vanguard along with the main assaulting force of the Imperial Army made their way to <a data-href="North Keep" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/locations/abanasinia/north-keep.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">North Keep</a>. In North Keep, Krynn's Vanguard looked for more information on <a data-href="Qualinost" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/locations/qualinesti/qualinost.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Qualinost</a> and the <a data-href="Darken Wood" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/locations/abanasinia/darken-wood.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Darken Wood</a> that laid ahead as they were making their way to Qualinost for the final showdown with the Alliance.<br>After debating whether or not to send a correspondence to <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Qualinesti Alliance/Claude Von Riegan.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/qualinesti-alliance/claude-von-riegan.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Claude</a>, Edelgard advised against it as they'd have the opportunity to talk with Claude before their conflict, as is customary.<br>Finding out that the Darken Wood was ruled by a Forestmaster and that the Forestmaster's followers fiercely defend the wood from outsiders, Krynn's Vanguard decided to venture in anyways and try to talk to the Forestmaster. After a while of traveling through the wood, a fog started to settle and they ran into a familiar face, <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Qualinesti Alliance/Marianne Von Edmund.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/qualinesti-alliance/marianne-von-edmund.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Marianne</a> of the Golden Deer. She explained that she'd been watching them since they entered the wood and that she'd been in service of the Forestmaster for quite some time even though she is of the Alliance. She explained that some monsters had recently been causing trouble in the wood and that if Krynn's Vanguard helped expel the monsters, the Forestmaster would ensure that they could pass through unimpeded.<br>Agreeing to help, Krynn's Vanguard fought a number of demonic beasts, giant wolves, and a wandering beast as well. The origins of these monsters are unknown but they have seen a couple of these monsters before. Standing about 20 feet tall the demonic beasts were also seen within the Holy Tomb when the Imperial Army first struck. The giant wolves appeared to be basic monstrosities, and the wandering beast appeared to have a decent level of intelligence, but never spoke. Defeating the beasts and coming out relatively unscathed, Marianne thanked them and sent them on their way as she walked into a thicker part of the wood and disappeared from sight.]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/session-notes/20.-september-28th,-2024-the-darken-wood.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/20. September 28th, 2024 The Darken Wood.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 07:14:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[21. October 5th, 2024 Retribution]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>After losing his title and escaping from his house arrest, <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Abanasinian Empire/Ludwig Von Aegir.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/abanasinian-empire/ludwig-von-aegir.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Duke Aegir</a> fled to Ordelia territory within the Alliance, and subsequently gathers a quiet militia under his command.<br>Meanwhile, Krynn's Vanguard runs into <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Qualinesti Alliance/Lysithea Von Ordelia.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/qualinesti-alliance/lysithea-von-ordelia.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Lysithea</a>, who has learned about and grown tiresome of Duke Aegir's men running amok in her family's territory. It's made clear that Lysithea actually supports the Empire and has no intention of stopping them, even offering to help them get to Qualinost faster. After they quell the rioting militia, they discover that Duke Aegir has been slain. In return for helping run Duke Aegir's men out of her territory and saving the villagers, Lysithea fulfills her promise of showing them a passage that will lead them to <a data-href="Qualinost" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/locations/qualinesti/qualinost.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Qualinost</a>. After everything calms down, she uses some unknown magic to split the fountain in the city in half, which reveals a passage that leads underground. Taking them down, she intends to lead them to Qualinost.]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/session-notes/21.-october-5th,-2024-retribution.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/21. October 5th, 2024 Retribution.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 07:14:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[22. October 19th, 2024 The Master Tactician]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>With help from <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Qualinesti Alliance/Lysithea Von Ordelia.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/qualinesti-alliance/lysithea-von-ordelia.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Lysithea</a>, Krynn's Vanguard and a large portion of the Imperial Army made their way to <a data-href="Qualinost" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/locations/qualinesti/qualinost.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Qualinost</a> for the final assault against <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Qualinesti Alliance/Claude Von Riegan.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/qualinesti-alliance/claude-von-riegan.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Claude</a>. Qualinost was under orders that no one would enter or leave the city. Claude and his army set-up in a naval port and planned to play defense against the Imperial army. Among the soldiers included <a data-href="Armantaro" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/krynns-vanguard/armantaro.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Armantaro</a>, a relative of Claude, and <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Qualinesti Alliance/HIlda Valentine Goneril.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/qualinesti-alliance/hilda-valentine-goneril.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Hilda</a>.<br>The battle began and it was obvious that it was going to be hard fought, but the party was pretty assured to take care of business. But Claude is cunning, and he'd secured the support of the Silvanesti king, <a data-href="Nader" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/qualinesti-alliance/nader.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Nader</a>, who brought a small fleet and a contingent of soldiers with him, making the battle tougher.<br>After taking Armantaro down, <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/The Black Eagles/Edelgard Von Hresvelg.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/the-black-eagles/edelgard-von-hresvelg.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Edelgard</a> asked him to join them. She wasn't the nicest about it, but it was the heat of battle and she'd seen only a fraction of what he could do, but saw great potential and wanted him on her side. She got what she wanted.<br>The fight continued and the battle seemed to turn a bit as Krynn's Vanguard is being pushed to their limit. Will they be able to pull out the victory and topple the Alliance?]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/session-notes/22.-october-19th,-2024-the-master-tactician.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/22. October 19th, 2024 The Master Tactician.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 07:14:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[23. October 26th, 2024 Capturing Qualinost]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>With the battle for Qualinost and control of the Alliance on the line, Krynn's Vanguard found themselves in a very precarious situation, surrounded on both sides and separated from their allies. With a few clutch spells from <a data-href="Big Bob" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/krynns-vanguard/big-bob.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Big Bob</a> and their new ally <a data-href="Armantaro" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/krynns-vanguard/armantaro.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Armantaro</a>, with a Stone Wall and a Scatter spell that flipped the battle to their side. This created a smaller area for the enemy to reach them and a choke point in their favor.<br>A few exchanges passed, and <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Qualinesti Alliance/Claude Von Riegan.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/qualinesti-alliance/claude-von-riegan.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Claude</a> flew in to try and end things quickly. He had a somewhat pleasant echange with <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/The Black Eagles/Edelgard Von Hresvelg.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/the-black-eagles/edelgard-von-hresvelg.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Edelgard</a> before he was eventually whittled down and conceded. With the party choosing to spare Claude and let him live, ever the opprotunist, he took off sweeping <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Qualinesti Alliance/Hilda Valentine Goneril.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/qualinesti-alliance/hilda-valentine-goneril.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Hilda</a> with him, and <a data-href="Nader" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/qualinesti-alliance/nader.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Nader</a> retreated along with the rest of his forces to from wherever they came with a couple of the ships still in tact.<br>Krynn's Vanguard took their new victory, although not taking all the prisoners they wanted, and set up an encampment in Qualinost, commandeering some of the unoccupied buildings for shelter. During their time after the battle, <a data-href="Volkhard Von Arundel" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/abanasinian-empire/volkhard-von-arundel.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Volkhard Von Arundel</a>, Edelgard's uncle, came and explained that he would be overseeing the Qualinesti Territory and it's administration and dissolution into the Empire alongside <a data-href="Count Leopold Von Bergliez" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/abanasinian-empire/count-leopold-von-bergliez.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Count Leopold Von Bergliez</a>, <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/The Black Eagles/Caspar Von Bergliez.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/the-black-eagles/caspar-von-bergliez.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Caspar</a> and <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Abanasinian Empire/Randolph Von Bergliez.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/abanasinian-empire/randolph-von-bergliez.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Randolph</a>'s father. After some questioning, the party couldn't tell what Arundel was hiding, but it was obviously something. Without being able to meet him, they could only assume that Count Bergliez is loyal to the Empire and has no ill intentions as he wants to see both of his son's succeed as they hold high rank within the Empire both militarily and politically. It was also revealed that Count Bergliez is the Minister of Military Affairs and focuses on that front while Arundel is more the diplomat, hence why they are working together on the effort. With it getting late, and not much more info to be gathered, Krynn's Vanguard and the remaining forces of the Imperial Army took to their temporary quarters and took a well deserved rest. For this is only the beginning.]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/session-notes/23.-october-26th,-2024-capturing-qualinost.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/23. October 26th, 2024 Capturing Qualinost.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 07:14:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[24. November 2nd, 2024 Siege of Relgoth]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>After capturing Qualinost and talking with <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Abanasinian Empire/Volkhard Von Arundel.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/abanasinian-empire/volkhard-von-arundel.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Lord Arundel</a>, the party spent a few days in Qualinost gathering supplies and resting as they awaited for <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Abanasinian Empire/Count Leopold Von Bergliez.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/abanasinian-empire/count-leopold-von-bergliez.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Count Bergliez</a> to arrive. After Edelgard spoke with him and they set out, Edelgard revealed her plan to them. They had announced that they were going straight for the Kingdom capital, <a data-href="Palanthas" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/locations/solamnia-and-the-northern-wastes/palanthas/palanthas.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Palanthas</a>. The majority of their army was, whereas the most elite of their force, along with the Black Eagles and Krynn's Vanguard would be heading to <a data-href="Relgoth" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/locations/solamnia-and-the-northern-wastes/plains-of-solamnia/cities/relgoth.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Relgoth</a>, a fortress city near the front lines. <br>After scouting and some reports, it was apparent that Relgoth housed a number of Kingdom generals. Among them were; <a data-href="Cornelia Arnim" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/cornelia-arnim.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Cornelia Arnim</a>, a mage of the royal court; <a data-href="Ingrid Brandl Galatea" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/ingrid-brandl-galatea.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Ingrid Brandl Galatea</a>, a noble who was once a student of the Officer's Academy at Garreg Mach Monastery in the Blue Lions house and friend of <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Holy Kingdom of Solamnia/Dimitri Alexandre Blaiddyd.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/dimitri-alexandre-blaiddyd.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dimitri</a>; <a data-href="Gwendal Roche" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/gwendal-roche.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Gwendal Roche</a>, a renown knight of House Rowe known as the Grey Lion; <a data-href="Felix Hugo Fraldarius" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/felix-hugo-fraldarius.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Felix Hugo Fraldarius</a>, the eldest son of House Fraldarius, longtime friend of Dimitri, and former student of the Blue Lion house; and <a data-href="Rodrigue Achille Fraldarius" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/rodrigue-achille-fraldarius.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Rodrigue Achille Fraldarius</a>, the head of House Fraldarius, a Kingdom General, and Felix's father. During this investigation, Krynn's Vanguard learned that Cornelia has some 'sweet children' that she was planning to use to defend Relgoth.<br>After determining that the city had prepared it's forces, the Imperial Army laid siege to Relgoth, and began advancing into the city with their elite forces. While tough, Krynn's Vanguard, along with help from <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/The Black Eagles/Edelgard Von Hresvelg.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/the-black-eagles/edelgard-von-hresvelg.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Edelgard</a> and the Imperial Army, managed to break through the south and east entrances to the city. They quickly found that they may be in for more than they bargained for as Cornelia's aforementioned 'sweet children' were Titanus. A mechanical and magical construct that is heavily fortified and stands 90 feet tall. Although they had not attacked yet, they were something they would eventually have to deal with, at least get past without getting essentially removed from the fight.<br>While fighting mostly front line soldiers, Krynn's Vanguard and their main forces faced off with Rodrigue and Felix, felling both while being pelted with Cornelia's Ice Storm from long range. Meanwhile, the smaller eastern force broke through the guard a the gate and rushed to get as close to Cornelia as possible before finding out that the city was littered with traps, as they encountered more resistance in their path to victory.]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/session-notes/24.-november-2nd,-2024-siege-of-relgoth.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/24. November 2nd, 2024 Siege of Relgoth.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 07:14:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[25. November 16th, 2024 The Silver Maiden]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>Slowly but surely, Krynn's Vanguard worked their way through the city, taking down key Kingdom targets in <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Holy Kingdom of Solamnia/Ingrid Brandl Galatea.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/ingrid-brandl-galatea.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Ingrid</a> and <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Holy Kingdom of Solamnia/Gwendal Roche.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/gwendal-roche.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Gwendal</a>. With 4 of their 5 major targets taken out, they set their sights on <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Holy Kingdom of Solamnia/Cornelia Arnim.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/cornelia-arnim.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Cornelia</a>.<br>Along the way, Krynn's Vanguard gained two allies in <a data-href="Arcadius" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/krynns-vanguard/arcadius.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Arcadius</a> returning after a small detour on his own journey and a friend that showed up with him, <a data-href="Nebula" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/krynns-vanguard/nebula.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Nebula</a>. It's unclear where the two went and how they came to find Krynn's Vanguard again, but that's a conversation for once the fight is over.<br>Pushing forward and taking out the front guard, Krynn's Vanguard has come face-to-face with the Titanus. Gargantuan constructs of massive power that are as durable as they are powerful. These large magical robots are able to land powerful strikes and even grapple a creature and continuously crush them in their grip. They are accompanied by somewhat powerful mages. Putting a dent in Krynn's Vanguard's forces, <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/The Black Eagles/Lindhardt Von Hevring.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/the-black-eagles/lindhardt-von-hevring.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Lindhardt</a> and <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/The Black Eagles/Caspar Von Bergliez.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/the-black-eagles/caspar-von-bergliez.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Capsar</a> popped out of existence being banished. They should at least be safe but it does slow them down. This isn't helped when <a class="internal-link" data-href="Krynns Vanguard/Valphire Roseblood.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/krynns-vanguard/valphire-roseblood.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Valphire</a> was knocked unconcious but was thankfully helped by Arcadius swooping in with his Griffin and saving the day. With them closing in, Cornelia is becoming a bit more active. Rather than just throwing out an Ice Storm in their general direction, her attacks are becoming more targeted. <br>Bound to be a hard fought battle and the prospect of death staring them in them down, can Krynn's Vanguard escape Relgoth unscathed?]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/session-notes/25.-november-16th,-2024-the-silver-maiden.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/25. November 16th, 2024 The Silver Maiden.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 07:14:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[26. November 23rd, 2024 Raelgoth's Defeat]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>Krynn's Vanguard had a hard-fought battle against <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Holy Kingdom of Solamnia/Cornelia Arnim.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/cornelia-arnim.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Cornelia</a> as she used the party's biggest weakness against them, targeting their mind rather than their bodies. She managed to incapacitate most of the party with a Psychic Scream spell and had them on the ropes before they finally broke through and took her down. She had taunted the party when they got into her sight "Oh my, what a charming guest. Let me take care of you...". As she fell, she lamented "So this is as far as I could get...All is in accordance with this carefully crafted script of ours...What a masterpiece! The ones that were being forced to dance around were in fact...us!" After she fell, her body transformed into the form of a slightly obese old man whose skin was as white as the scales on a newly hatched white wyrmling. There were streaks of black in his hair, and the eyes were also purely white with no iris or pupil. The eyes were only defined by black outlines on his face.<br>After declaring victory, <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/The Black Eagles/Edelgard Von Hresvelg.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/the-black-eagles/edelgard-von-hresvelg.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Edelgard</a> led the Imperial Army alongside the rest of the Black Eagles and Krynn's Vanguard as they entered the Plains of Solamnia on the road to Palanthus. At their camp, they were approached by <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Abanasinian Empire/Volkhard Von Arundel.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/abanasinian-empire/volkhard-von-arundel.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Lord Arundel</a> who told them that it might have been better to keep Cornelia around as an ally, and that he hoped "The Empire doesn't become another Relgoth" whatever that meant. The meaning was quickly figured out at <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/The Black Eagles/Hubert Von Vestra.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/the-black-eagles/hubert-von-vestra.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Hubert</a> came to report that Relgoth had been disintegrated by 'Pillars of Light' and that it was likely the work of what happened at Vash in the recent past, circa 250 A.C. <br>South of the old Alliance territory there is a valley where the earth is always aflame. Once, javelins of light fell from the sky there... They pierced the earth and set the forest ablaze, creating a land of torment. We believed it may have been the work of the goddess, Sothis, but... It was actually an attack by Those Who Slither In the Dark.<br>Those Who Slither In the Dark (TWSITD (pr. twisted)), are a nefarious group that has only been spoken about, but have not been encountered aside from the revealed form of Cornelia. Through some probing of Edelgard and <a data-href="Armantaro" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/krynns-vanguard/armantaro.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Armantaro</a>, it was revealed that the real Cornelia is more than likely dead as having 'two' Cornelia's alive could cause issues later down the line.<br>Armed with this new info, Edelgard asked Krynn's Vanguard if they'd be willing to snuff out TWSITD after they defeated <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/The Church of Seiros/Lady Rhea.md#The Immaculate One" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/the-church-of-seiros/lady-rhea.html#The_Immaculate_One" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Immaculate One</a>. They agreed and she thanked them. Now, it was time to rest and be ready to march on Palanthas in the coming days.]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/session-notes/26.-november-23rd,-2024-raelgoth's-defeat.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/26. November 23rd, 2024 Raelgoth's Defeat.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 07:41:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Session Notes]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br>]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/session-notes/session-notes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/Session Notes.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 07:13:28 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>