<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Dragonlance]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/</link><image><url>https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Dragonlance</title><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/</link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 14:04:09 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 14:04:09 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[Lemish]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The current Dictator of Lemish is Lord Tyrian Shattersword, a cruel master who prefers to rule through brute force – a language the population understand just fine, having used it themselves for generations. With the coming of the war Tyrian has chosen to ally himself with the Dragonarmies, and so his keep is now adorned with the<br>
banners of the Blue Wing.<br>Lemish is no city of struggling and oppressed innocents, but rather it was populated already with bandits, rogues and other opportunistic peoples out to satisfy only their own greed. Most are happy to throw their lot in with the Dragonarmies, whilst those who are not are only disappointed that a larger, stronger and crueler force has been able to take over (which they would do themselves if they were that powerful).<br>Roads lead into the city of Lemish from the south, north-west and north-east, each guarded by squat three-story gray towers that stand astride the roads, their parapets manned at all times Dragonarmy soldiers keeping an out for danger. All travelers are stopped at these towers so that they and their wagons can be searched before proceeding to the city. Upon a completed search, each traveler is then given a token which can be given to the guards at the city gate to show that they have been searched.<br>Two units of Draconians man each of these towers – one on guard along the parapets and one on the ground conducting searches. All of these has a blue crystal whistle strung<br>
around their necks to sound an alarm.<br><br><br>There are three organized factions of thieves and rogues within Lemish, all competing for wealth and power. Other than the Split Silverpieces, membership or association with any of these organizations is punishable by death.<br><br>The only guild to have received an official sanction from the Dragonarmies to continue existing, the Split Silverpieces have made a good profit taking contracts directly from Lord Tyrian, doing the dirty work he would prefer not be tied directly to him or his armies.<br><br>Before the Dragonarmies came the Phantoms made a good living as road bandits and highwaymen, but they have been forced to keep a low profile since the roads became watched. Now they are merely petty thieves and pickpockets.<br><br>Operating across the southern coast of Solamnia and Lemish, the Blue Circle are primarily out for themselves. They are primarily con artists and crooked merchants, but well armed and well trained for hunting down and forcing payment from their debtors.<br>The local Blue Circle are led by a Half-Elf named Lareen, who is very defensive about her group being the smallest of the Blue Circle cells in the area. She is actually pretty sympathetic to the Dragonarmies as she hates Solamnia and her own people (the Qualinesti), but she does not seek official sanction for her operations because values her<br>
independence a lot more.<br><br><br>A large stone warehouse no the city’s north side has been converted for use by the young Dragon Topaz, it’s interior fitted out with arid stone walls and floor to create a more comfortable environment for her, given her distaste for the woodland of Lemish. The design is such that the walls trap heat within the warehouse, yet Topaz still seems to hate the setup.<br>Directly adjacent to the warehouse is a richly appointed apartment with a balcony that looks out into the warehouse’s interior. This apartment is the private residence of Lukas Daerlath, a local Dragonarmy champion.<br><br>Visitors will be hard-pressed to find an honest merchant here, and those who are not local are far more likely to encounter con-men who spot them for outsiders and charge extremely high prices for even basic necessities.<br>Prices in Lemish are likely to be four to five times higher than the norm, and often for products that are half the quality.<br><br>Though not proclaimed as a major industry, many merchants in Lemish deal in slaves. Previously these were merely the captives of bandit raids and those brought in by<br>
pirates. Since the War of the Lance, the Dragonarmies have been importing more and more captives from across Ansalon, and this trade has flourished.<br><br>An old temple to Kiri-Jolith now lies as a desecrated ruin, the only part that hasn’t been scrawled on or smashed being the graveyard, which has been respectfully left alone (though<br>
this is partly due to superstition). Explorers find the ruin a collection of broken walls, scattered boulders and a few surviving floors and the corners of upper levels.<br>The many vantage points in these ruins makes it an ideal meeting place for the Blue Circle, as they can meet and speak without prying eyes, and any intruders who do come find themselves in the perfect position to be ambushed.]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/locations/lemish/cities/lemish.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Locations/Lemish/Cities/Lemish.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 02:23:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Abanasinian Empire]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br>]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/abanasinian-empire/abanasinian-empire.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NPCs/Abanasinian Empire/Abanasinian Empire.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 18:42:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ludwig Von Aegir]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Ludwig.jpg" src="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/ludwig.jpg"><br>
Personality Traits: Proud, authoritative, and pragmatic. Ludwig commands respect and carries himself with an air of nobility and power.<br>Ideals: Order and tradition. He believes in maintaining the established social order and upholding the traditions of the Abanasinian Empire.<br>Bonds: Loyal to the Empire and his family, particularly his son, <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/The Black Eagles/Ferdinand Von Aegir.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/the-black-eagles/ferdinand-von-aegir.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Ferdinand</a>. He has complex relationships with other noble houses.<br>Flaws: Stubborn and power-hungry. Ludwig is resistant to change and often prioritizes his own power and status over the needs of others.<br>Backstory: Ludwig von Aegir was the Prime Minister of the Abanasinian Empire and the head of House Aegir, one of the most powerful noble families in the Empire. Known for his political acumen and influence, Ludwig has played a key role in maintaining the stability and traditions of the Empire. He is a strict and demanding father to Ferdinand, expecting him to uphold the family's prestigious legacy. Ludwig's ambition and desire for power often put him at odds with other nobles and the ruling family, particularly after Edelgard ascends to the throne. His resistance to Edelgard's reforms and his own machinations for power create tension within the Empire, setting the stage for the conflicts to come. As of current, he is being held on very strict house arrest within the Empire and has been stripped of his duties as Prime Minister. None of this is known to the people of the Empire.]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/abanasinian-empire/ludwig-von-aegir.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NPCs/Abanasinian Empire/Ludwig Von Aegir.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 22:55:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/ludwig.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/ludwig.jpg"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Volkhard Von Arundel]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Arundel.jpg" src="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/arundel.jpg"><br>
Personality Traits: Calculating, manipulative, and ambitious. Volkhard is a master strategist who hides his true intentions behind a facade of nobility.<br>Ideals: Power and control. He seeks to consolidate power and influence within the Abanasinian Empire and beyond.<br>Bonds: Loyal only to himself and his allies. He uses his connections and family ties to further his own agenda.<br>Flaws: Deceitful and untrustworthy. Volkhard is willing to betray anyone to achieve his goals and often underestimates the potential for resistance against his plans.<br>Backstory: Volkhard von Arundel is a high-ranking noble of the Abanasinian Empire. As the uncle of Edelgard, he took on the role of regent after her father's health declined, effectively controlling the Abanasinian Empire from the shadows. He orchestrated numerous schemes to further his group's agenda. Volkhard he appears to be a supportive and caring uncle, but his true motives are sinister. By the beginning of the war phase, his machinations have set the stage for widespread conflict, aiming to destabilize Ansalon and pave the way for his group's dominance.<br>Status: Alive]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/abanasinian-empire/volkhard-von-arundel.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NPCs/Abanasinian Empire/Volkhard Von Arundel.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 17:50:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/arundel.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/arundel.jpg"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>