<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Dragonlance-Sync]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Dragonlance-Sync</title><link/></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 22:21:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 22:21:38 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[37. March 1st, 2025 The Stolen Artifact]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>As Krynn's Vanguard got engulfed in the whiteout blizzard, they encountered this being that had changed form so many times and proceeded to defend themselves as it moved forward. It wasn't necessarily chasing after them as much as it just so happened that they were in its way. After a while, they managed to fend it off for long enough that the storm they got caught in had passed.<br>Travelling further they came across some ruins of what looked to have once been a medium sized castle, or keep of sorts. This place had given way to time and the elements that only a portion of the first floor stood. Entering inside, they found a large foyer that had caved-in on itself that the stairways to higher levels were broken and blocked off by the rubble creating a more natural shelter. There was a stairway that led down however.<br>Investigating downstairs, they found five doors. Two on either side, and one at the end of the hall. Making their way through the rooms, they found a study with an empty wine rack, a fireplace, a desk with nothing of note, and a small sitting area with a small bookcase filled with books in draconic that after flipping through a few, were all for leisure rather than knowledge. The next room hosted a small kitchen, and another a bedroom. These rooms were also immaculately clean, and any attempt to dirty them were magically whisked away leaving them immaculate. The last room was locked and all of their attempts to break down the door, pick the lock or any other method failed. Moving to the last room, it was a grand room that held the husk of a silver dragon, and an altar at the back.<br>Approaching the dragon husk, the door behind them disappeared as it awakened with a holy flame filling in where its body used to be. This undead dragon was NOT happy. After some words asking the theives to "Give it back" it engaged in combat. After defeating the dragon and laying it to rest as best they could, the altar was found to have a hollow platinum triangle that once investigated, empowered <a data-href="Kyan Covverre" href="krynns-vanguard/kyan-covverre.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Kyan Covverre</a>'s Amulet of the Devout more than it already was. Casting Legend Lore, the party learned that Paladine had tasked this dragon with protecting a piece of the Crest of the Daughters of Paladine. After such a long life, the dragon took the noble act of embracing undeath to continue its duty as there would be nothing left if it continued in its current form.<br>With all that settled, the party rested, and headed to Icewall Castle in the form of Wind Walk with help from <a data-href="Armantaro" href="krynns-vanguard/armantaro.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Armantaro</a>. The party saw that the keep was heavily fortified with White Abishai, Dragon Army soldiers, likely some officers as well, it was hard to tell specific ranks from their vantage point, dragonnells, and an assortment of white dragons. This was obviously a base of operations, and more than likely where the stolen piece was kept. It was time to strategize, and more than likely fight.]]></description><link>session-notes/37.-march-1st,-2025-the-stolen-artifact.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/37. March 1st, 2025 The Stolen Artifact.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 22:09:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[38. March 9th, 2025 Infiltrating Icereach Castle]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>Krynn's Vanguard stood atop the falling parts of Icereach Castle concocting a strategy on how exactly they would enter the area. After investigating and finding some suitable ledges to stand on, they reverted back from their Wind Walk forms and found some windows that they melted the ice off of and pushed the window open.<br><a data-href="Kyan Covverre" href="krynns-vanguard/kyan-covverre.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Kyan Covverre</a> and <a data-href="Big Bob" href="krynns-vanguard/big-bob.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Big Bob</a> created a platform to go down the immense structure with Fabricate and Creation. Meanwhile, <a data-href="Armantaro" href="krynns-vanguard/armantaro.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Armantaro</a> used Telekinesis to move the platform.<br>As they descended into the darkness, they were ambushed by a Young White Dragon. After a bit, the dragon knocked them off of the platform sending them plummeting to the ground where they were greeted by another Young White Dragon, a pair of Sivak Draconians, White Dragon Wyrmlings, Kapak Draconians, and Remorhaz.<br>Dealing with the multiple threats in an enclosed space caused a few issues but Krynn's Vanguard managed to fell their foes. Gathering their bearings, they could hear the army from outside approaching so they moved along. Going down a set of stairs, they encountered another issue. Only this time, it was larger...and deadlier. They were greeted bye a Sivak Draconian, a Baaz Draconian, and an Ancient White Dragon. This battle took a lot of the party's resources and health, even knocking <a data-href="Valphire Roseblood" href="krynns-vanguard/valphire-roseblood.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Valphire Roseblood</a> out of commission for a bit, but again, Krynn's Vanguard emerged victorious.<br>The castle kept leading down and eventually, they came to a door that was coated with ice. However, this door was easily able to be pushed open. What awaits Krynn's Vanguard? Money? Treasure? Relaxation? Maybe something more sinister. More dragons? The leader of the White Dragon Army? Only one way to find out.]]></description><link>session-notes/38.-march-9th,-2025-infiltrating-icereach-castle.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/38. March 9th, 2025 Infiltrating Icereach Castle.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 22:09:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[39. March 22nd, 2025 Defeating The White Dragonarmy]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>The great double doors of Icewall Castle groaned open, the iron hinges shrieking beneath centuries of frost. A howling wind surged through the crack, throwing snow into the hall like a crashing wave. The torches on the wall flicker and die in an instant—snuffed by the bite of unnatural cold.<br>The grand hall unfolded before Krynn's Vanguard like a tomb of ancient royalty. Pillars of blue-white ice stretch to the vaulted ceiling, supporting arches strung with icicles the size of spears. Light filtered dimly through frozen stained glass, painting fractured halos across the permafrost-slick floor. Every breath hurts. Lungs sting. Armor chills. And weapons groan with creeping frost.<br>At the far end of the hall, a throne carved from a single slab of jagged ice towers like a claw. Seated upon it is a figure swathed in white and silver—Feal-Thas, his eyes as pale and piercing as the blizzard outside. His presence stills the air itself. The snow does not dare touch him.<br>And bhind the throne, half-shadowed in a plethora of ice and poweder snow, Akis rises and unfurling his wings as the temperature drops even lower. With each breath, the expected steam immediately crystalizes in a thin sheet of ice that drops to the floor shattering on impact.<br>Feal-Thas rose slowly.<br>
Feal-Thas (his voice low, echoing through the frost):<br>
“So… the child returns. And not alone. How quaint.”
<br>His gaze fell upon <a data-href="Orla" href="krynns-vanguard/orla.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Orla</a>—his child. There is no kindness in his face. Only cold judgment.<br>
Feal-Thas:<br>
“I thought you would be wiser than to trespass here. But then… wisdom was never your strength. You chose heat over heritage. Fire over frost. You chose them.”
<br>The air tightens. Snow drifts along the seams in the floor. And then—<br>
Akis (chuckling, voice like iron dragged across stone):<br>
“I rather like them, Feal-Thas. They’ve come dressed for war, but they wear grief in their eyes. Will it be yours… or theirs?”
<br>Feal-Thas lifts a hand. Snowflakes rise unnaturally around it—hovering like tiny blades.<br>
Feal-Thas:<br>
“You stand in Icewall, where the air bends to my will. Where the snow obeys. You cannot hide your heartbeat from me… I feel its panic.”
<br>He begins to descend the dais. Each step creaks with a sound like cracking glass. The temperature plunges further. Even your thoughts begin to slow.<br>
Feal-Thas:<br>
“You seek the crest? A shard of Paladine’s favor? I hold more than that. I hold your truth. Your beginning. And perhaps…”
<br>He pauses—then snaps his fingers.<br>Suddenly, shards of ice spiral from the ground, forming a half-cage around you. The walls moan with the strain of ancient magic.<br>
Feal-Thas:<br>
“…your end.”
<br>
Akis (grinning wide):<br>
“I say we skip the sentiment, old elf. Let the cold test their convictions. Let them earn their gods.”
<br>Feal-Thas turns slowly back to his child. The snow around him falls dead still.<br>
Feal-Thas:<br>
“Speak. Beg. Fight. It matters little. But know this: if you take one step closer…”
<br>
His voice hardens like the ice beneath your feet.<br>
“…you are no longer my child. You are my enemy.”
<br>The cold deepens. The wind screams through cracks in the walls. The floor trembles with rising power.<br>And with a deafening crack—the battle begins.<br>Feal-Thas was mainly dealt with by Orla and <a data-href="Orion" href="krynns-vanguard/orion.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Orion</a>. He was much weaker without Akis giving him a massive assist. Unclear why Akis let the Dragon Highlord go down so easily, it was likely he'd outlived his usefulness. Orla finished him off by slicing Friekugel across his abdomen, before torquing her hips back around with another swing cleaving through his neck, snapping the spinal cord and sending his head rolling. In his final words he almost begged<br>
“Protect her…”
<br>The battle raged on, all of the party members now focused on the White Son of Takhisis, revived and more powerful than ever. <a data-href="Arcadius" href="krynns-vanguard/arcadius.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Arcadius</a> with his Blessed Dragonlance contributed massively to the fight even if he did end up loosing his life a couple times due to being directly targeted by the greatwyrm. <a data-href="Big Bob" href="krynns-vanguard/big-bob.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Big Bob</a> and <a data-href="Kyan Covverre" href="krynns-vanguard/kyan-covverre.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Kyan Covverre</a> were right there able to revive him and keep him kicking as it was vital to have him with them. A turning point in the fight was when Akis had all of them on the ropes, one more Cold Breath attack likely downed most, if not all of the party marking their defeat. Kyan pulled out a Mass Heal basically giving everyone a second life.<br>Akis fell and as the party gathered their breath, Orla was suddenly batted against the far wall as Akis' tail whipped around and he rose once more. In a blinding gale of ice and wind, Akis merges with Takhisis’s polar wrath. Its body crackles with frozen power, radiating a lethal chill that can freeze enemies solid. His Blizzard Apotheosis activating bringing him second life. The fight was on again and the attacks he unleashed were even more brutal. The effects of being in his lair caused an extra layer of hindrance. What transpired in just under 10 minutes felt like hours, but Krynn's Vanguard defeated the ancient greatwyrm, Orion dealing the final blow. He brought his warhammer down on the dragon's skull, causing it to splinter. The shockwave from the impact as Akis's Cold Breath billowed in his throat caused the neck of the dragon to crack and split, slattering blood all over the snow and ice of the room as he fell...for the second, and final time. No resurgence, no sneaky tail attacks...just quiet.<br>Resting and gathering their bearings, they searched the room after the ice and snow powered by Akis' magic faded and melted, giving the room warmth and protection from the frigid wasteland outside the walls. Remembering her father's last words, Orla and Orion searched the walls trying to find the 'her'. Using Speak With Animals, Orla was able to communicate with Athena. Meanwhile, <a data-href="Valphire Roseblood" href="krynns-vanguard/valphire-roseblood.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Valphire Roseblood</a> and Kyan opened the chest that was burried beneath the ice. They found 5,000 gold pieces, the Piece of Querrasian, the Copper piece to the Crest of the Daughters of Paladine. Four down, three to go.<br>Offering assistance, Bob and Kyan moved away some stone to find Athena. A ladder led down to a storage unit where they found a fairly scared, but well-cared for Tibetan Mastiff. Taking them up, they made sure to give her food and water and Athena seemed to immediately get attached to Orla.<br>Gathering what they could see outside, the blizzard had somewhat cleared but all they could see was a number of white dragons laying in the snow, unmoving. It was unlcear if they were resting or not. Bob worked on trying to get the magic out from the Fundementum. It was quite the struggle as the beach-ball sized mass was almost pure, raw, untamed, natural magic, but with his skill, Bob was able to pull out some of it, storing what he could in vials. It could probably be used to create some sort of potion, but exactly what needed time and research to be determined.<br>The group debated for a long time on whether to leave or to rest as, to their knowledge, there was an army waiting for them outside. They barred the doors and windows taking a rest. It was fairly uneventful as Bob continued to work with the fundementum during his watch, and the others didn't really do too much. It was close, but Krynn's Vanguard was lucky to survive the past few days with their lives, and all their allies.]]></description><link>session-notes/39.-march-22nd,-2025-defeating-the-white-dragonarmy.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/39. March 22nd, 2025 Defeating The White Dragonarmy.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 22:10:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[40. March 29th, 2025 Next  Steps]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>After returning to Dargaard Keep, Krynn's Vanguard gathered their bearings and restocked on what goods they can, even sending a message to their old companion, Dott, in Kalaman to get some potions they were looking to acquire to pair with <a data-href="Big Bob" href="krynns-vanguard/big-bob.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Big Bob</a>'s own potions. <br>It took some planning but after discussion, they decided to trek towards Thorbardin by teleporting to The Tower of High Sorcery in Wayreth...because that worked out so well the last time. Through some odd happenings, or a sick joke by the Weave, Krynn's Vanguard found themselves in a somewhat abandoned, but likely being torn down to move, Black Dragon Army camp. They were surrounded by 3 Black Dragon Wyrmlings which seemed easy enough, until their backup came. A Pit Fiend accompanied by A Green, Blue, and Red Abishai. That made things a lot tougher. <a data-href="Armantaro" href="krynns-vanguard/armantaro.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Armantaro</a> dealt with the hard hitting innate lightning of the Blue Abishai with a lucky banishment and the rest of the group tore into the wyrmlings and other devils. <a data-href="Valphire Roseblood" href="krynns-vanguard/valphire-roseblood.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Valphire Roseblood</a> ended up being killed by the Green Abishai before the rest of the group had to bail out back to Dargaard Keep. With a Wish spell from Armantaro, they retrieved Valphire's slightly vulture picked body and brought her back. However, she would be staying at Dargaard Keep to look over the place as she sustained a lasting injury that Bob's Raise Dead could not heal. <br>Resting up and recouping, it was time to decide how they wanted to proceed to Thorbardin.]]></description><link>session-notes/40.-march-29th,-2025-next-steps.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/40. March 29th, 2025 Next  Steps.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 22:21:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Session Notes]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br>]]></description><link>session-notes/session-notes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/Session Notes.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 22:20:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[East Road]]></title><description/></item></channel></rss>