<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Dragonlance]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Dragonlance</title><link/></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 02:27:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 02:27:58 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[Kalaman]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img src="lib/media/pasted-image-20240326120732.png"><br><br>Kalaman, the Beacon of the East, is one of the largest cities in Solamnia. Far from the nation’s heartland and the capital of Palanthas, the city is a bastion of trade and safety at the edge of the province of Nightlund.<br><br>Capital City.&nbsp;Kalaman is the capital of the Solamnic province of Nightlund.<br>Ancient Bastion.&nbsp;Kalaman is a thriving trade city known for its strong walls, castle, and harbor beacons, all of which predate the Cataclysm.<br>Rulers.&nbsp;The city is led by a governor, a council of prominent guild leaders, and a military marshal.<br>Military.&nbsp;Kalaman maintains a significant military force to deter raiders from Estwilde and monsters from the Dargaard Mountains.<br>Vingaard Port.&nbsp;The city sits at the mouth of the Vingaard River, about thirty miles downriver from Vogler.<br><br>Kalaman is led by the following three groups:<br>Governor.&nbsp;The head of Kalaman’s government is Governor Calof Miat (lawful neutral, human&nbsp;<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://www.dndbeyond.com/monsters/16966-noble" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="https://www.dndbeyond.com/monsters/16966-noble" target="_blank">noble</a>). He represents the city’s people and speaks on their behalf during council sessions.<br>Guild Leaders.&nbsp;A council composed of the leaders of the city’s five most prominent guilds—the Cartographers’ Guild, Dockhands’ Guild, Fishers’ Guild, Masons’ Guild, and Shipwrights’ Guild—oversees the city’s broad business interests and runs varied public services. The guilds’ leaders are neutral human and hill dwarf&nbsp;nobles&nbsp;who are prone to bickering and jockeying for influence.<br>Marshal.&nbsp;Kalaman’s military guards the city and defends eastern Solamnia. The military is robust, as the city can’t afford to solicit aid from the Knights of Solamnia, headquartered in the west, every time raiders from Estwilde or other threats cross the border. Kalaman’s military is commanded by the pragmatic Marshal Nestra Vendri (lawful neutral, human&nbsp;knight).<br><br><br>A symbol of the city, the age-old fortress of Castle Kalaman rises atop rugged cliffs, visible from anywhere within the city walls and for miles beyond. The city’s governor dwells within the castle, and the ruling council holds its meetings here. Castle Kalaman also serves as the headquarters of Kalaman’s military, and its barracks can house hundreds of troops. Extensive catacombs run beneath Castle Kalaman, but the entrances to these tunnels were closed long ago and remain magically sealed.<br><br>Merchants from across Ansalon do business in Kalaman’s thriving bazaar. Characters can purchase any&nbsp;equipment from the&nbsp;Player’s Handbook&nbsp;here. Vendors from far-off lands—like Ergoth or Mount Nevermind—often bring rare curios here to trade.<br><br>Twin forges stand across the street from one another, run by the dwarven cousins Kadmos and Tiria Hammerstrike (both lawful neutral, hill dwarf&nbsp;veterans. While both are competent smiths, Kadmos specializes in armor and Tiria excels with weaponry.<br><br>The walls of Kalaman extend several hundred feet into the city’s harbor. The tower at each end holds a prominent beacon surrounded by an array of lenses. These beacons were created before the Cataclysm by the city’s Istarian founders, and the light from their flames cuts through the densest fog.<br><br>At any time, dozens of ships are anchored along the busy docks of Kalaman’s harbor. Small local fishing ships vie for harbor space alongside mighty seafaring vessels, some from far-off lands. Every day there’s a 10 percent chance a merchant ship from a distant land puts into port here, its crew eager to sell unique wares and tell tales of danger on the sea.<br><br>Meulara’s Oddities is a small shop piled with trinkets. Its shopkeeper, Meulara (chaotic good, kender&nbsp;commoner) is a silver-haired woman with a bright smile. Meulara claims to know every kender in the city, and most kender new to town are directed to her so they can swap stories and news from their travels.<br><br>The Steady Beacon is a tavern that boasts a large taproom, a fish-focused menu, and modest lodging. Its decor features the broken weapons of defeated bandits. The tavern is a favorite of Kalaman’s soldiers, and most evenings, dozens of off-duty troops relax here. The inn’s owner, Jesen Thold (neutral good, human&nbsp;veteran), is a friend of Marshal Nestra Vendri, head of Kalaman’s military.<br><br>Outside the city to the east and west sprawl trade camps. These expanses of ramshackle buildings began as campgrounds for caravans. Over time, the tents were replaced by simple buildings aligned along muddy streets. They now house hundreds who can’t find lodgings within the city’s walls.<br><br>Wyhan (lawful evil, human&nbsp;mage) is a black-robed Mage of High Sorcery. Though supposedly retired, she keeps a shop that deals in wares few in Kalaman need. Wyhan’s Apothecary sells the occasional good-luck charm, but those who know what to ask for might gain access to the apothecary’s back room, which houses esoteric spell components. ]]></description><link>locations/solamnia-and-the-northern-wastes/nightlund/kalaman.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Locations/Solamnia and the Northern Wastes/Nightlund/Kalaman.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 19:34:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib/media/pasted-image-20240326120732.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib/media/pasted-image-20240326120732.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>