<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Dragonlance-Sync]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Dragonlance-Sync</title><link/></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 03:52:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 03:52:22 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[31. January 11th, 2025 Ominous Winds]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>After a hard fought battle, Krynn's Vanguard was able to defeat the 2 Solars and Angel of Paladine they found in the underwater Tower of High Sorcery. The Angel of Paladine flew up, away from the group proclaiming "Enough. You have proven your mettle. Take this and go." The angel pulled an amulet off his neck and tossed it towards the group. <a data-href="Arcadius" href="krynns-vanguard/arcadius.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Arcadius</a> caught the amulet and immediately the group appeared back at Dargaard Keep.<br>This amulet was an oddly shaped piece of Bronze. It was immediately obvious they had obtained another piece of The Crest of the Daughters of Paladine. Three down, four to go, and they know the general location of one. Arcadius felt the petrified Bronze Dragon egg he'd obtained start to shift and move on it's own. He set it down and after a few moments, it hatched with a Bronze Wyrmling emerging. It looked over the group, specifically Arcadius, gave a small roar, and took off to the skies, flying north. This happened before when they obtained the Silver piece back in <a data-href="Qualinost" href="locations/qualinesti/qualinost.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Qualinost</a>. Are the pieces and these eggs connected? Time will tell.<br>With not many other directions to go, the group spent a couple days recouping at their keep, before teleporting back to Qualinost to do a bit of research. After a long debate, the decided that after the mishap that happened last time, they would travel on foot. Their destination was Than-Khal. They were curious what awaited them in Kharolis. As far as they were aware, it had been ravaged by the Cataclysm but somewhat revitalized afterwards.<br>On their way, they ran into a patrol of Dragonarmy troops. Nothing too bad, 4 Baaz Draconians led by some sort of Dragon-like humanoid creature they hadn't seen before. It seemed to be more intelligent than the Baaz Draconians as it was able to speak common and snuff out that the group, who used <a data-href="Armantaro" href="krynns-vanguard/armantaro.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Armantaro</a>'s Seeming spell to appear as Baaz Draconians, was not sent by Takhisis herself as they said. The Dragon Queen has no need to concern herself with foot soldiers. She has other business to attend to.<br>After taking them out, they came across an odd tree that had part of it cut out that it looked like the gaping maw of a creature. It was different from the other trees. Upon further inspection, the group found a hole that led down to a cave system. As they went down, they came to a fork in their path. One path leading left, the other right, and they heard the sound of some sort of creature, but couldn't determine the path. Does danger lie ahead? Maybe a hidden civilization? The only way to know is to press forward.]]></description><link>session-notes/31.-january-11th,-2025-ominous-winds.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/31. January 11th, 2025 Ominous Winds.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 03:51:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Session Notes]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br>]]></description><link>session-notes/session-notes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/Session Notes.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 03:19:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[East Road]]></title><description/></item></channel></rss>