<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Dragonlance-Sync]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Dragonlance-Sync</title><link/></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 17:49:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 17:49:05 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[30. January 4th, 2025 The Search]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>As summer begins to take hold in Krynn, Krynn's Vanguard left Palanthas and the Imperial Army to build (and rebuild) their territory as the headed back to Dargaard Keep for much needed rest. After gathering their bearings and supplies they went back to <a data-href="Qualinost" href="locations/qualinesti/qualinost.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Qualinost</a> with the help of <a data-href="Armantaro" href="krynns-vanguard/armantaro.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Armantaro</a>'s Teleportation and did some research in the library trying to find information on Those Who Slither in the Dark (TWSITD), and The Abyssal Concord that they've heard about. Not much information was to be found as both entities tend to work from behind the scenes.<br>WIthout any luck, they intended to head to the <a data-href="Tower of High Sorcery at Wayreth" href="locations/qualinesti/tower-of-high-sorcery-at-wayreth.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Tower of High Sorcery at Wayreth</a> to see what they could find and hunt for more pieces of The Crest of the Daughters of Paladine. A small mishap with Armantaro's Teleport took them to another, very similar tower, in a very different location. The party arrived at the bottom of the ocean, in a magically domed area, with just the ocean floor and the tower there. <br>Heading inside, the party found a fairly empty tower, with a staircase on either side that hugged the wall as it curled up the the next floor. The rest of the floor was empty, but the stonework, the layout, and everything about the tower was immaculate. With the light in the tower, even the white marble floor seemed to sparkle.<br>At the top 5th floor, the party was finally greeted with a set of wooden double doors. On the doors were the symbols of the good gods in the form of a half-circle, with a large symbol of Paladine in the center that split when the doors opened.<br>Upon entering the room. They saw a figure in blue and gold armor with their back to them. With a few words, he greeted them, then challenged them to combat along with two solars.<br>It seemed that Krynn's Vanguard needs to prove themselves worthy to obtain another piece of the Crest of the Daughter's of Paladine. Can they prove worthy? Or will the power of a servant of the Gods overpower them?]]></description><link>session-notes/30.-january-4th,-2025-the-search.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/30. January 4th, 2025 The Search.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 03:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[31. January 11th, 2025 Ominous Winds]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>After a hard fought battle, Krynn's Vanguard was able to defeat the 2 Solars and Angel of Paladine they found in the underwater Tower of High Sorcery. The Angel of Paladine flew up, away from the group proclaiming "Enough. You have proven your mettle. Take this and go." The angel pulled an amulet off his neck and tossed it towards the group. <a data-href="Arcadius" href="krynns-vanguard/arcadius.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Arcadius</a> caught the amulet and immediately the group appeared back at Dargaard Keep.<br>This amulet was an oddly shaped piece of Brass. It was immediately obvious they had obtained another piece of The Crest of the Daughters of Paladine. Three down, four to go, and they know the general location of one. Arcadius felt the petrified Brass Dragon egg he'd obtained start to shift and move on it's own. He set it down and after a few moments, it hatched with a Brass Wyrmling emerging. It looked over the group, specifically Arcadius, gave a small roar, and took off to the skies, flying north. This happened before when they obtained the Silver piece back in <a data-href="Qualinost" href="locations/qualinesti/qualinost.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Qualinost</a>. Are the pieces and these eggs connected? Time will tell.<br>With not many other directions to go, the group spent a couple days recouping at their keep, before teleporting back to Qualinost to do a bit of research. After a long debate, the decided that after the mishap that happened last time, they would travel on foot. Their destination was Than-Khal. They were curious what awaited them in Kharolis. As far as they were aware, it had been ravaged by the Cataclysm but somewhat revitalized afterwards.<br>On their way, they ran into a patrol of Dragonarmy troops. Nothing too bad, 4 Baaz Draconians led by some sort of Dragon-like humanoid creature they hadn't seen before. It seemed to be more intelligent than the Baaz Draconians as it was able to speak common and snuff out that the group, who used <a data-href="Armantaro" href="krynns-vanguard/armantaro.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Armantaro</a>'s Seeming spell to appear as Baaz Draconians, was not sent by Takhisis herself as they said. The Dragon Queen has no need to concern herself with foot soldiers. She has other business to attend to.<br>After taking them out, they came across an odd tree that had part of it cut out that it looked like the gaping maw of a creature. It was different from the other trees. Upon further inspection, the group found a hole that led down to a cave system. As they went down, they came to a fork in their path. One path leading left, the other right, and they heard the sound of some sort of creature, but couldn't determine the path. Does danger lie ahead? Maybe a hidden civilization? The only way to know is to press forward.]]></description><link>session-notes/31.-january-11th,-2025-ominous-winds.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/31. January 11th, 2025 Ominous Winds.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:01:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[32. January 18th, 2025 The Creatures Below]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>Krynn's Vanguard continued down the path they found below the illusionary tree and found nothing more than an ordinary cave. Damp, musty, and with nothing more than normal cave sounds. Continuing forth they found a fork in the road. One path leading left, the other leading right.<br>After an Augury spell by <a data-href="Armantaro" href="krynns-vanguard/armantaro.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Armantaro</a>, the party went right as that was their best option. A while later they stumbled upon a dead end. Investigating, this seemed to be a natural cave-in. Looking further, <a data-href="Big Bob" href="krynns-vanguard/big-bob.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Big Bob</a> could see there was a path on the other side thanks to his Truesight. After clearing the blockage, they found a man-made staircase that led downward into a system of rooms. Unsure of what this place was they continued and were ambushed by Gazers. They were quickly dispatched of and the group continued investigating. They didn't find much besides debris and crumbling books from centuries of decay. Armantaro did find a book cover well enough in tact to make out the words "The Soul, The Blood, The Breath, and the Bones." The remainders of the pages had some words, but it was too old for any of the torn and decaying state of the book to make any sort of sense or guess out of it. <br>They came to a locked door they needed the key to. After searching and being attacked by a group of Spectators, they circled back to the other path they hadn't taken where they found two pieces of a broken key. On their way back to the locked door, they were attacked by a Dragonflesh Gafter, and a Dragonflesh Abomination...just what was this place?<br>Proceeding through the locked door they found a throne room of sorts, investigating, they found a hidden contraption within the throne that opened up a secret passage. The group continued without impediment until they found yet another fork. Choosing fairly arbitrarily, the group stumbled into a room with a Dragon Skeleton, the skeleton animated and some other creatures materialized. The group did battle with a Dragonbone Golem, Animated Breath, a Dragonblood Ooze, and a Draconic Shard. The Draconic Shard was a massive problem that they dealt with first, but not before it took down <a data-href="Valphire Roseblood" href="krynns-vanguard/valphire-roseblood.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Valphire Roseblood</a> who lost their life relatively quickly after that. One of their main healers, Bob was out of comission for most of the battle being restrained by the Golem. After dispatching the rest of the enemies, <a data-href="Kyan Covverre" href="krynns-vanguard/kyan-covverre.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Kyan Covverre</a> was able to revivify Valphire and they healed up, pressing forward again.]]></description><link>session-notes/32.-january-18th,-2025-the-creatures-below.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/32. January 18th, 2025 The Creatures Below.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 17:14:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[33. January 25th, 2025 The Eternal Altar]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>After the scare of almost loosing a party member, Krynn's Vanguard took to the last room where they found a massive skull with a singular, natural looking hole in the center above the massive jaw. Moving closer, it animated with a ghostly glow around it. The creature put up a good fight incapacitating a few of the party members, but with it being undead, it was no match for <a data-href="Arcadius" href="krynns-vanguard/arcadius.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Arcadius</a>' Holy Avenger. After a swift strike through the eyehole, the Death Tyrant's now inanimate skull slid down the Holy Avenger's blade and fell to the ground after Arcadius withdrew his sword.<br>The party found yet another secret door that they went through where they found nothing but a plain looking altar at the back of the room. Before even getting into the room they were attacked by a massive beholder who was even more problematic than the Draconic Shard of the Death Tyrant. After some unfortunate luck, <a data-href="Armantaro" href="krynns-vanguard/armantaro.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Armantaro</a> was killed. After the party defeated the beholder, it was too late to save him.<br>Meanwhile, while the party was fighting, Armantaro awoke in a room made of white marble with black vein patterns. Exiting two double doors with silver looking knockers he came to a balcony that overlooked a foyer. Two curved staircases on either side led down to five sets of double doors. One at the front, which looked to be an entrance of sorts, two on the left, and two on the right. Entering the first one on the left, he came to a study. A fireplace was lit and burning with two ornate chairs decorated with a mix of copper, brass, bronze, silver, gold, and oddly enough...platinum. There was a figure who sat in the chair, it spoke before Armantaro had a chance. "So...you've arrived. Sooner than expected I must admit. But I'm glad we finally get the chance to talk." The figure stood revealing itself to be a platinum dragonborn. A not often used, but known aspect of the Dragon Father, Paladine.<br>He and Armantaro spoke and Armantaro made amends with Paladine, accepting his position as one of Paladine's champions. With that, Armantaro awoke, given new life by the Patron Deity of gods of Good.<br>Investigating the altar, <a data-href="Kyan Covverre" href="krynns-vanguard/kyan-covverre.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Kyan Covverre</a> used his diving blessings to learn that this was a lost relic known as the Eternal Altar. This altar, given power by Gilian, the God of Knowledge, allowed the party to ask one, singular question, and it would give the answers. Aligning with their quest, they asked where they could find the remaining pieces of the Crest of the Daughters of Paladine. They had 3 of the seven peices, and needed three more. They were told the Piece of Querrasian, could be found in Icereach, the Piece of Haraineer was in Silvanesti, The Piece of Aurora was in the Dragonhead Isles, a location north of Ansalon, and the Shard of Reorx was in Thorbardin.<br>Armed with this information, the party rested, and left out an alternate enterance they found, which was the other path they could have taken. Leaving the illusionary tree behind, they set out towards Icereach as a Gaseous Form, making a stop at Than-Khal. Upon reaching the area, expecting to find a rebuilt, thriving town and a place to rest, plan, and prepare for their jouney, they were met with the Dragonarmies. Specifically, they encountered a Green Abishai leading five Baaz Draconians who were on patrol. Could their luck be any worse?]]></description><link>session-notes/33.-january-25th,-2025-the-eternal-altar.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/33. January 25th, 2025 The Eternal Altar.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 17:16:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[34. February 1st, 2025 Than-Khal's Secrets]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>Krynn's Vanguard were fighting against a band of Bazz Draconians led by a Green Abishai when they suddenly all felt something hit them in the back and before they knew it, they were all ensnared in nets. Unable to move or use any of their equipment to escape, they were knocked out and dragged off somewhere.<br>They awoke in a damp, musty dungeon locked behind bars that seemed to have some sort of protection against magic and were also too close together for someone small to squeeze through. Although they couldn't see them, they were able to overhear some guards talking. They talked about how they'd been stuck down here for over a week but at least now there were prisoners. They shot the breeze for a bit talking about how one of them was going to go to the orchard and pick some fruit, while the other was a bit too short to reach the branches. They also talked about the Highmaster and how they seemed to have a VERY large tree in their orchard. This was slang talk for a brothel and how the Highmaster was probably in bed with the Highlord.<br>Continuing, they talked about a silvanesti elf who ran a black market of sorts within Than-Khal where soldiers were able to get some things that weren't exactly allowed. The party, needing a boat, found this very intriguing. There was also mention of a new logistics coordinator who came over from another dragonarmy and seemed to take his job way too seriously. They mentioned the name Andarin Holt.<br>A few moments passed until someone came down and told the guards that their relief was on the way and that he'd watch over them for now. After they'd left, the guard came down to the party's cell and lowered their hood revealing the chisled, wartorn, and hardened face of <a data-href="Darrett Highwater" href="npcs/darrett-highwater.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Darrett Highwater</a> now 5 years removed from the Kalaman war. After telling them that he was working undercover, he told them of a path to escape that had been carved out. They needed to move quickly as there was a couple more guards coming but Darrett unlocked their cell and let them go through the path to escape. It took a while as they ran into some guards but some quick thinking and planning, they were able to steal a small boat that Darrett had prepared with their missing equipment and make their way to Icereach.<br>Getting up the Icewall was somewhat of a challenge but they were able to make the climb. After some planning and divine interaction, they started making their way towards where they believed Icewall Castle to be, their best chance to find the next piece. Along the way, they came across a part of the ground that was outcropped and seemed like it could be a makeshift shelter of sorts. After exploring for a bit and finding some doors and rooms that seemed to house a small community, they came across a large common area. They ran into some Traag Draconians, a few White Dragon Wyrmlings, and an Adult White Dragon. Without much conversation, they attacked. Being not the brightest creatures, they viewed the invasion of their home as not a simple mistake.]]></description><link>session-notes/34.-february-1st,-2025-than-khal's-secrets.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/34. February 1st, 2025 Than-Khal's Secrets.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 17:48:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Session Notes]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br>]]></description><link>session-notes/session-notes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/Session Notes.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 17:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[East Road]]></title><description/></item></channel></rss>