<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Dragonlance]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/</link><image><url>https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Dragonlance</title><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/</link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 15:17:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 15:17:22 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator></dc:creator><item><title><![CDATA[DM 2. April 6th, 2024 The Boilers 1]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>Back in their cells, the party tried to use some of the rusty weapons around to pick the locks but were unsuccessful. Orion, with his newfound power, summoned a spectral wyrmling who, with a bit of guidance, was able to free the party. Picking up some pretty worn and blunt weapons, they exited the prison chamber in search of their gear, and possibly their captors.<br>Upon exiting, they heard a group of men presumably having a grand time and more than likely drunk. They spotted some bandits, the same ones that had captured them participating in what could only be described as Tavern-like activities such as arm wrestling.<br>Pryderion disguised himself as a bandit and tried to rile them up by alerting them that their horses were being stolen. Unsuccessful in this attempt, he was challenged to an arm-wrestling match by Gadion, the self-proclaimed "Strongest Bandit on all of Krynn". Gadion made quick work of Pryderion and sent him to the boilers.<br>Tehv'in was the next to challenge Gadion after being spotted trying to sneak by. Gadion humored him with a best of 3 arm-wrestling match which he won 2-1. Gadion, just planning to mess with the Githyanki gave him the opprotunity to draw from a deck of cards. After drawing and showing the card to Gadion, a large diamond appeared on the table as the card disappeared. Gadion offered the diamond and the cards to Tehv'in if he could get his friend out from a somewhat ominous room called "The Boilers".<br>In the boilers, as it's name suggested, it was quite warm, very warm in fact. After a bit of inspection, both Tehv'in and Pryderion noticed the smell of sulfur, which grew stronger with a small gust of wind that blew every so often, almost rhythmically. It was odd as this room was supposedly underground with no outlet except for the door up top.<br>Tehv'in slipped on a loose part of the ground and landed on what could only be described as a large pile of coins and other valuable items. It seems they'd stumbled upon a dragon's hoard. Score! If only it weren't being guarded...by a dragon. After a bit of questioning, the dragon lit up sconces in the room and revealed itself to be a gold dragon by the name of Mydass. <br>Mydass explained that the bandits had taken over this place and she had only not expelled them because she was tied to her duty of protecting the hoard, in case her mother, Aurora, ever came back. She'd been waiting for millennium for this to happen. In that time, she'd fallen into a deep slumber. In exchange for expelling the bandits, Mydass agreed to reward them with a small portion of the hoard. As they didn't have many weapons, Mydass armed them with tow +2 longswords and a +3 longbow. Tehv'in and Pryderion charged in and Orion joined the frey with the help of one of the +2 longswords and the three quickly disposed of the bandits and found all their equipment in a nearby storeroom.<br>Upon returning the weapons, Mydass rewarded them with 4,100 copper pieces, 14,000 silver pieces, 210,000 gold pieces (Ryan's jaw dropped upon hearing this), and 4,200 platinum pieces. In addition, they were given the skull of a pit fiend, an ornately decorated spinning top, an hourglass filled with sparkling sand, an assortment of gems totalling 1,050 gold pieces, 11 pieces of art totaling 275 gold pieces, a spell scroll of Wish, as spell scroll of True Resurrection, and a Ring of Invisibility.<br><br>After resting for a day in Karoc-Tor, the party set out to Hargoth while stopping in Connersby as they passed through. In the town square, a man in vestments stood uptop some crates speaking in a language they did not understand. Asking one of the elderly residents, they learned the man was preaching about The <a data-href="Church of Seiros" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/church-of-seiros.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Church of Seiros</a>, a fairly new religion to Krynn that was quickly speading. Apparently Seiros was a god from another dimension that chose to watch over Krynn and work to restore order while the other gods had turned their backs on the world. Inspired by this, Pryderion decided to dedicate his life to this Goddess.<br>Arriving in Hargoth, the party learned that there were some knights from Northern Ergoth that had arrived a few days ago and were repairing their ship, and restocking while in port before heading back to Northern Ergoth. A portly barkeep told them they called themselves the Knights of Seiros.<br>The party went to talk to these so-called knights and met with their leader <a data-href="Alois Rangeld" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/alois-rangeld.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Alois Rangeld</a>. Alois told them all about the Knights of Seiros and even recruited Pryderion, giving him a set of their armor, which bore the Holy Symbol of Seiros and her crest on the left breast, on top of the heart.<br>The knights still needed a few days to get ready, but they'd be ready to leave in a couple days.]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/session-notes/dm-session-notes/dm-2.-april-6th,-2024-the-boilers-1.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/DM Session Notes/DM 2. April 6th, 2024 The Boilers 1.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 14:19:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>