<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Dragonlance-Sync]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Dragonlance-Sync</title><link/></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 03:23:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 03:23:54 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[Dargaard Keep]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Dargaard Keep is a massive and ancient fortress built high on the cliffs at the northern end of the Dargaard mountain range, a week's journey from the port city of Kalaman to the north. The structure consists of a thick curtain wall, five guard towers built along the curtain wall, a four-story central keep, and a five-story tower rising from the keep itself.<br><br>Dargaard Keep was ruined by a fire caused by an earthquake the day of the Cataclysm. Nearly every room in the keep shows clear signs of this damage. The walls and floors are scorched. Wood and cloth are burned and blackened. Black soot covers most surfaces. The smell of smoke and burning bodies is ever-present.<br><br>The ceilings in Dargaard Keep are 15 feet high.<br><br>Ghostly white flames still burn in the sconces around the keep, offering an eerie, cheerless illumination.<br><br>The walls surrounding the Keep are 30 feet high. The wall is broken in several places that allow entry.<br><br>The Keep's walls are one-foot-thick granite. The doors are made of oak that has deteriorated from age or been damaged or destroyed by fire.<br><br>The floors of the keep are covered with a layer of dark ash mixed with dust. Even though Soth and his minions have occupied the keep for over 300 years, the ash is undisturbed.<br><br>Krynn's Vanguard defeated Lord Soth circa early 354 A.C. approximately a year and a half after they stopped the floating citadel from reaching <a class="internal-link" data-href="Kalaman.md" href="locations/solamnia-and-the-northern-wastes/nightlund/kalaman.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Kalaman</a> and lead the defense of the siege of Kalaman taking out Kansaldi Fire-Eyes and expelling the Red Dragon Army from the region. They made a stop at Dargaard Keep on request from <a class="internal-link" data-href="../../../NPCs/Marshal Vendri.md" href="npcs/marshal-vendri.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Marshal Vendri</a> on their way to <a class="internal-link" data-href="../Palanthas/Palanthas.md" href="locations/solamnia-and-the-northern-wastes/palanthas/palanthas.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Palanthas</a>.<br>Krynn's Vanguard was told they could keep anything and everything they found in the keep, including the keep itself. Currently, the Foresworn are repairing and maintaining the keep as well as the surrounding lands as they are expecting settlers from Malegoth, whom are among the refugees from <a data-href="Vogler" href="locations/solamnia-and-the-northern-wastes/hinterlund/vogler.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Vogler</a>.<br>The once-barren plains of Nightlund are now a verdant expanse of fertile farmland, dotted with crops of wheat, vegetables, and orchards. Clear streams wind through the landscape, and the rejuvenated forests are alive with wildlife. The oppressive gloom has lifted, replaced by vibrant skies and fresh air.<br>Dargaard Keep, formerly a symbol of fear, now stands as a beacon of hope. Its walls have been repaired and adorned with banners of the Forsworn, representing peace and renewal. Inside, the keep is a bustling hub of activity. The Great Hall has been repurposed as a communal space for gatherings, while once-ominous chambers now serve as libraries, workshops, and places of worship.<br>At the foot of the keep, the town has risen from its ruins. Streets are repaired and lined with colorful homes, shops, and communal gardens. A lively marketplace thrives in the town square, where townsfolk sell fresh produce and handcrafted goods. Festivals and music now fill the air, where silence and fear once reigned.]]></description><link>locations/solamnia-and-the-northern-wastes/nightlund/dargaard-keep.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Locations/Solamnia and the Northern Wastes/Nightlund/Dargaard Keep.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 03:04:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[East Road]]></title><description/></item></channel></rss>