<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Dragonlance-Sync]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Dragonlance-Sync</title><link/></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 23:57:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 23:57:16 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[38. March 9th, 2025 Infiltrating Icereach Castle]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Krynn's Vanguard stood atop the falling parts of Icereach Castle concocting a strategy on how exactly they would enter the area. After investigating and finding some suitable ledges to stand on, they reverted back from their Wind Walk forms and found some windows that they melted the ice off of and pushed the window open.<br><a data-href="Kyan Covverre" href="krynns-vanguard/kyan-covverre.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Kyan Covverre</a> and <a data-href="Big Bob" href="krynns-vanguard/big-bob.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Big Bob</a> created a platform to go down the immense structure with Fabricate and Creation. Meanwhile, <a data-href="Armantaro" href="krynns-vanguard/armantaro.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Armantaro</a> used Telekinesis to move the platform.<br>As they descended into the darkness, they were ambushed by a Young White Dragon. After a bit, the dragon knocked them off of the platform sending them plummeting to the ground where they were greeted by another Young White Dragon, a pair of Sivak Draconians, White Dragon Wyrmlings, Kapak Draconians, and Remorhaz.<br>Dealing with the multiple threats in an inclosed space caused a few issues but Krynn's Vanguard managed to fell their foes. Gathering their bearings, they could hear the army from outside approaching so they moved along. Going down a set of stairs, they encountered another issue. Only this time, it was larger...and deadlier. They were greeted bye a Sivak Draconian, a Baaz Draconian, and an Ancient White Dragon. This battle took a lot of the party's resources and health, even knocking <a data-href="Valphire Roseblood" href="krynns-vanguard/valphire-roseblood.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Valphire Roseblood</a> out of commission for a bit, but again, Krynn's Vanguard emerged victorious.<br>The castle kept leading down and eventually, they came to a door that was coated with ice. However, this door was easily able to be pushed open. What awaits Krynn's Vanguard? Money? Treasure? Relaxation? Maybe something more sinister. More dragons? The leader of the White Dragon Army? Only one way to find out.]]></description><link>session-notes/38.-march-9th,-2025-infiltrating-icereach-castle.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/38. March 9th, 2025 Infiltrating Icereach Castle.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 23:56:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Session Notes]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br>]]></description><link>session-notes/session-notes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/Session Notes.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 23:56:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[East Road]]></title><description/></item></channel></rss>