<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Dragonlance]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/</link><image><url>https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Dragonlance</title><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/</link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 21:21:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 21:21:58 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[57. October 18th, 2025 The Tree's Secret]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>Inside the tree, The party encounterd a winding root system shrouded in a blue/purple hue that also colored the root system. There were a number of caverns to explore, some only being a few feet deep, others stretching on.<br>After debating and picking one of the caverns, the party was left in darkness, with the tree's 'walls' seeming to move on their own and pulse lightly. Almost as if something was breathing, or the tree itself was a breathing being. The walls were somewhat soft and moist to the touch. Eventually, the party reached a room of pillars with a pit that seemed to stretch on forever, one pillar in the back of the room rose 30 feet above the others, with a chest on top. The pillars were slippery. Falling down the pit, you were eventually grabbed by something, and your vision went black, before you were placed back at the entrance of the room.<br>As Krynn's Vanguard does, they overthought what the seemingly empty chest meant before they found a false bottom, and bolts anchoring it to the floor. Removing the bolts, the party found a secret passage behind the chest. Taking the passage, the party encountered a waterfall of blood that trapped them in vines made of blood and seemed to want to eat them, until the party offered to take them to see more of the world outside of the abyss. The party casted out Eumenius' soul from the medallion they had, and took the blood spirit, thing with them.<br>Moving on, they came to a cavern that was obviously the inside of something. There were two parallel lines of people, eyes glazed over lining a path for them to a door. What was behind the door was likely the center of a Mind Flayer colony...what the hell have they gotten themselves into?]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/session-notes/57.-october-18th,-2025-the-tree's-secret.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/57. October 18th, 2025 The Tree's Secret.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 22:17:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[East Road]]></title><description/></item></channel></rss>