<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Dragonlance]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/</link><image><url>https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Dragonlance</title><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/</link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 22:18:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 22:18:51 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[56. September 20th, 2025 Bastagaal's Aftermath]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>Krynn's Vanguard had defeated Malgorzeth, The Lord of Chains and returned back to the library which was empty, save for only themselves and the books. Outside, Looking East, Krynn's Vanguard could see all the people of Bastagaal in their grey robes, seemingly frozen in time. Looking west, the city was barren, not a soul to be seen. No matter where they went in the city, looking East was like walking through a picture, and looking West made the city a ghost-town.<br>After visiting the tavern, which was the same scene, the party reached the center of town as it started to split apart at the seams. Pieces fell and launched into the air creating a chaotic obstacle course to navigate as they had to make their way out of the town or be swallowed whole by whatever was destroying the city. Making it out, the city fell into the abyss...further into the Abyss maybe.<br>Making their way further away from the city, they encountered a forest whose trees seemed to be withered and carved out with what looked to be crude faces with gaping mouths and hollw eyes. The forest fell into an unnatural fog with specs of something white falling like snow that seemed to make the fog rise. Some creatures were seen out of the corners of the party's eyes but when they looked over, the creatures were gone. And the giggling that came with them was unsettling in of itself. After walking for a while, the party happened upon a large tree, 300 feet high and 100 feet across, with the same face-like features almost inviting them in. The party stepped through, only able to guess what was next]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/session-notes/56.-september-20th,-2025-bastagaal's-aftermath.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/56. September 20th, 2025 Bastagaal's Aftermath.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 22:07:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[57. October 18th, 2025 The Tree's Secret]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>Inside the tree, The party encounterd a winding root system shrouded in a blue/purple hue that also colored the root system. There were a number of caverns to explore, some only being a few feet deep, others stretching on.<br>After debating and picking one of the caverns, the party was left in darkness, with the tree's 'walls' seeming to move on their own and pulse lightly. Almost as if something was breathing, or the tree itself was a breathing being. The walls were somewhat soft and moist to the touch. Eventually, the party reached a room of pillars with a pit that seemed to stretch on forever, one pillar in the back of the room rose 30 feet above the others, with a chest on top. The pillars were slippery. Falling down the pit, you were eventually grabbed by something, and your vision went black, before you were placed back at the entrance of the room.<br>As Krynn's Vanguard does, they overthought what the seemingly empty chest meant before they found a false bottom, and bolts anchoring it to the floor. Removing the bolts, the party found a secret passage behind the chest. Taking the passage, the party encountered a waterfall of blood that trapped them in vines made of blood and seemed to want to eat them, until the party offered to take them to see more of the world outside of the abyss. The party casted out Eumenius' soul from the medallion they had, and took the blood spirit, thing with them.<br>Moving on, they came to a cavern that was obviously the inside of something. There were two parallel lines of people, eyes glazed over lining a path for them to a door. What was behind the door was likely the center of a Mind Flayer colony...what the hell have they gotten themselves into?]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/session-notes/57.-october-18th,-2025-the-tree's-secret.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/57. October 18th, 2025 The Tree's Secret.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 22:17:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Session Notes]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br>]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/session-notes/session-notes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/Session Notes.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 21:57:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[East Road]]></title><description/></item></channel></rss>