<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Dragonlance-Sync]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Dragonlance-Sync</title><link/></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 22:26:52 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 22:26:52 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[35. February 8th, 2025 Icereach's Blizzard]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>Krynn's Vanguard finished off the dragon, wyrmlings, and draconians in the newly settled lair and looted the place. They didn't find too much out of the ordinary, but did come across some very useful items. They found a Rope of Mending, a Ring of Mind Shielding, and a Potion of Invulnerability. There was also a fair amount of coin to boot.<br>After leaving the cave, they kept traveling. However, they'd noticed that since they'd exited, a mighty blizzard had overcome the area. They could see about 15 feet in front of them before it became a whiteout, and it was so cold that their cold weather gear wasn't enough to keep them warm. However, <a data-href="Big Bob" href="krynns-vanguard/big-bob.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Big Bob</a>, being ever resourceful, had potions of warmth that kept everyone warm and comfortable in the harsh environment.<br>Another cave caught their interest as they passed by. This was naturally formed unlike the last and had a peculiar purple-toned ice about 2 inches thick over the walls. Any attempt to break or melt the ice was futile. Along the walls of this short outcropping of land, there was a mural along the walls. It depicted many a figures whose carvings seemed to be painted in either blue, yellow, or red. After looking through all the murals, <a data-href="Armantaro" href="krynns-vanguard/armantaro.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Armantaro</a> deduced that this mural depicted the Age of Starbirth, particularly with the depiction of Takhisis corrupting the first metallic dragons into her own chromatic dragons, and Paladine and Reorx working together to make another batch of metallic dragons. These first dragons were known as the Sons of Takhisis, and the Daughters of Paladine. They were said to have perished ca. 9000 PC with the Sons of Takhisis hunting the Daughters of Paladine. They methodically took down all the dragons leaving the gold dragon, Aurora the last one standing. With clever thinking and mastery of her abilities, she was able to take down all of them, sacrificing herself in the process as she entangled herself with the red dragon Furyion, turned herself to stone, and drowned Furyion as he was unable to escape the now petrified dragon's grasp.<br>After finding what seemed like a statue made of ice at the back of the cave, the party left. They noted that the statue looked oddly familiar to the angel they'd fought at the bottom of the ocean. Along the way, they were ambushed by an icy-like figure that resembled a wraith, it was a tough battle and as it was about to deal the killing blow to Armantaro, a light broke through and with a thundering voice, "NOT TODAY" the Icewraith was destroyed, and the party spared the loss of a comrade.<br>Without much info to go on, and being unable to navigate a raging blizzard, the party marched on to wherever they'd end up next.]]></description><link>session-notes/35.-february-8th,-2025-icereach's-blizzard.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/35. February 8th, 2025 Icereach's Blizzard.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 22:26:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Session Notes]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br>]]></description><link>session-notes/session-notes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/Session Notes.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 17:32:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[East Road]]></title><description/></item></channel></rss>