<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Dragonlance-Sync]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Dragonlance-Sync</title><link/></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 19:31:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 19:31:34 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[42. April 12, 2025 The Kingdom of Dwarves (cont.)]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>Krynn's Vanguard continued exploring Thorbardin, exploring the floor below the one they started on and clearing out a number of monsters before their options ran out and they returned to the previous floor. Going to the west, they again encountered a number of devils, most notably a Balor who seemed to be overseeing the operations of this floor.<br>They did find a few dwarves whom were seeking refuge and since they'd been mapping it out, they were able to show them the way out as far as they knew so they could meet up with other dwarves who were also trying to get out of dodge.<br>Crossing the bridge on what is known as Floor 4, they fought against a Marilith and a Nalfeshnee who were putting up a good fight. That didn't last for long though as <a data-href="Armantaro" href="krynns-vanguard/armantaro.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Armantaro</a> sent the Nalfeshnee off the bridge plummetting below to it's death.<br>What else awaited Krynn's Vanguard?]]></description><link>session-notes/42.-april-12,-2025-the-kingdom-of-dwarves-(cont.).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/42. April 12, 2025 The Kingdom of Dwarves (cont.).md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 18:56:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[43. April 19, 2025 The Kingdom of Dwarves (cont.)]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>Krynn's Vanguard continued to clear out the floor coming across a puzzle of locked doors that had three circular indents in it. They eventually learned that it was unlocked by inserting three signet rings into the doors. The only issue was finding said signet rings.<br>Exploring more, they actually met a Succubus who, surprisingly, wasn't interested in fighting, nor seducing any of them. Instead, she was going to hide out here for a while before she could sneak away and get back to her own tasks from whence she came. She did reveal to the party that all the monsters and demons were here on the orders of the Prince of Demons. A name they hadn't heard before. Perhaps they'd learn more talking to some of the demons. Unlikely, but worth a shot.<br>Krynn's Vanguard cleaned up this floor and found a spot that was enough out of the way, not too bloody, and didn't contain many dead dwarf remains to rest for the night before continuing on.]]></description><link>session-notes/43.-april-19,-2025-the-kingdom-of-dwarves-(cont.).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/43. April 19, 2025 The Kingdom of Dwarves (cont.).md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 19:09:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[44. April 26, 2025 The Kingdom of Dwarves (cont.)]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>Continuing on after resting, Krynn's Vanguard took the stairs down the the next floor where they were greeted with a path to the left, a path to the right, and some slightly ajar doors in front of them. Moving forward, they came into a room with a number of undead who were quickly disposed of. This was a throne room of sorts and after investigating, they noticed that some of the statues didn't line up with the correct order of the Thorbardin Kings. After rearranging them into the correct order. The one standing statue revealed a hidden compartment holding a dwarven signet ring. Maybe there were more locks that had the same locking mechanism they'd heard of earlier?<br>Leaving this throne room of sorts they took the left path that led to a number of monsters, along with a dwarf that was missing her ledger. After some exploring, the party found and returned her ledger. It was full of transactions between the Thorbardin bank and it's customers. She promptly followed the party's escape route as they went to the right to clear that path.<br>They quickly came across two Nalfeshnee who didn't offer much information before attacking, and were quickly dispatched with a lucky Banishment from <a data-href="Armantaro" href="krynns-vanguard/armantaro.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Armantaro</a>. Moving forward, their next challenge was a Pit Fiend, which turned out to be two Pit Fiends. One was quickly dealt with and the party was about to decend all their might on the second.]]></description><link>session-notes/44.-april-26,-2025-the-kingdom-of-dwarves-(cont.).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/44. April 26, 2025 The Kingdom of Dwarves (cont.).md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 19:22:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Session Notes]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br>]]></description><link>session-notes/session-notes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/Session Notes.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 18:48:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[East Road]]></title><description/></item></channel></rss>