<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Dragonlance-Sync]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Dragonlance-Sync</title><link/></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 18:31:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 18:31:55 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[47. May 31th, 2025 The Kingdom of Dwarves]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>After dealing with the Black Puddings and making their way East along the bottom half of the floor, Krynn's Vanguard spotted a sleeping Balor in an open area, they tried to sneak back as to not wake the fiend and made their way into another room that <a data-href="Arcadius" href="krynns-vanguard/arcadius.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Arcadius</a> had detected had 2 fiends inside. They encountered a Horned Devil and Erinyes that were quickly dispatched of. Arcadius also detected some undead in a room to the south. As they tried to sneak past the Balor to explore the Southwest portion of the floor, the Balor opened its eyes as if it had known the group was there and attacked...but it wasn't alone.<br>As the battle ensued, the party was attacked by three Skittering Horrors along with a Red and Blue Abishai that joined shortly after the Balor started the fight. It was now obvious that major threats could lurk around every corner, and that they can't let their guard down even the slightest, as it might mean their downfall.<br>After clearing out the large monsters and gathering their bearings, the party pushed forward to clear out the rest of the floor.]]></description><link>session-notes/47.-may-31th,-2025-the-kingdom-of-dwarves.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/47. May 31th, 2025 The Kingdom of Dwarves.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 18:25:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[48. June 7th, 2025 The Kingdom of Dwarves]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>Krynn's Vanguard found a room that was covered in blood, they weren't sure if this was monster blood or the blood of dwarves, but it was obvious this was a very, very bloody encounter. Unfortunately this turned out to be dwarven blood as in the room next door the party found dwarves hung like buthered animals, drained of their blood. A sight they'd seen before, but it never gets easier. Clearing the last part of the floor the party dealed with the undead they detected earlier. Thankfully, that was an easy fight. They took a moment to rest and heal up before debating where to go next.<br><a data-href="Kyan Covverre" href="krynns-vanguard/kyan-covverre.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Kyan Covverre</a>, thanks to his preparedness, was making rough maps of all the areas they had visited and laid it out for the party. They decided that if they were going to get to the bottom of what happened here, they needed to go deeper, so they took the path down to what they had aptly dubbed 'Floor 9'.<br>Immediately upon reaching the bottom of the stairs to Floor 9, there truly was no rest for the weary as they were greeting (very aggressively) by not one but two Balors who almost seemed to be waiting for them. Before they could even try dimplomacy, their words were cut off with heavy, and largely targeted attacks. They'd dealt with one before, but two? Could be a rough challenge if they aren't careful.]]></description><link>session-notes/48.-june-7th,-2025-the-kingdom-of-dwarves.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/48. June 7th, 2025 The Kingdom of Dwarves.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 18:28:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Session Notes]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br>]]></description><link>session-notes/session-notes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/Session Notes.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 18:31:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[East Road]]></title><description/></item></channel></rss>