<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Dragonlance-Sync]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Dragonlance-Sync</title><link/></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 02:32:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 02:32:43 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[27. December 7th, 2024 The Field of Revenge]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>As Krynn's Vanguard entered the Plains of Solamnia. They used Clairvoyance to spy on the contingent of people they saw in the distance and found that the Knight's of Seiros, led by <a data-href="Lady Rhea" href="npcs/the-church-of-seiros/lady-rhea.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Lady Rhea</a> was at the helm of their leadership along with <a data-href="Catherine" href="npcs/the-church-of-seiros/catherine.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Catherine</a>. They communed with nature in a somewhat roundabout fashion, and were told it wasn't particularly a great idea to try and disguise themselves as Kingdom soldiers or Knights of Seiros.<br>Ignoring this advice, they disguised themselves as Kingdom soldiers after much discussion and once they were behind enemy lines, they met with Lady Rhea, now going by the name Seiros, who promptly figured out their ruse (making this NOT a war crime) and dispelled their disguises and sending them back from whence they came.<br>This prompted the battle to begin where the Kingdom Army had arrived, and carried out their plan of flanking The Imperial Army and Krynn's Vanguard with the Church at the Eastern and Southern flanks.<br>The battle commenced with Krynn's Vanguard fighting against the commanders <a data-href="Sylvain Jose Gautier" href="npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/sylvain-jose-gautier.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Sylvain Jose Gautier</a>, <a data-href="Mercedes von Martritz" href="npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/mercedes-von-martritz.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Mercedes von Martritz</a>, <a data-href="Dedue Molinaro" href="npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/dedue-molinaro.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dedue Molinaro</a>, and <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/Holy Kingdom of Solamnia/Dimitri Alexandre Blaiddyd.md" href="npcs/holy-kingdom-of-solamnia/dimitri-alexandre-blaiddyd.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">King Dimitri Alexandre Blaiddyd</a> on the Kingdom of Solamnia's side, with Seiros/Rhea on the Church's side.<br>After one of the Kingdom soldiers transformed into a demonic beast, most of the party was put under a charm effect by Rhea where they were forced to assist the Church and attack their comrade's while <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/The Black Eagles/Edelgard Von Hresvelg.md" href="npcs/the-black-eagles/edelgard-von-hresvelg.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Edelgard</a> made it her mission to take down Rhea herself dealing massive blows and getting her on the ropes. Sylvain was doing his best to assist but was struggling, especially after most of the party afflicted by the charm broke free due to their own will, or was assisted by another member. The demonic beast was not helping the party gain any ground and they were locked at a choke point.<br>Meanwhile, <a data-href="Orla" href="krynns-vanguard/orla.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Orla</a> and <a class="internal-link" data-href="NPCs/The Black Eagles/Caspar Von Bergliez.md" href="npcs/the-black-eagles/caspar-von-bergliez.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Caspar</a> went straight for Mercedes and while she took a lot of hits, she and those with her were holding their own and Mercedes was able to recover a significant amount of her health.<br>Will Krynn's Vanguard survive and march on Palanthas? Or will they fall here and need the Hands of Time to be rewound once more to give rise to a new set of unlikely heroes?]]></description><link>session-notes/27.-december-7th,-2024-the-field-of-revenge.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/27. December 7th, 2024 The Field of Revenge.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 02:32:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The History of the Marks]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The enigmatic Marks hold a paramount place in the lore of Ansalon, shaping the continent’s history, society, and power structures. These mystical emblems, inherited through bloodlines, grant their bearers extraordinary abilities and have deeply influenced Ansalon’s religious, political, and cultural development.<br><br>The origins of Marks trace back to ancient times, shrouded in myth and legend. According to the Church of Seiros, Marks were bestowed upon humanity by the goddess Sothis. These divine gifts were believed to be symbols of the goddess’s favor, granting extraordinary powers and marking the bearers as exceptional individuals chosen to lead and protect Ansalon.<br>The Church’s teachings recount the story of Nemesis, the so-called King of Liberation, who, along with his Ten Elites, wielded the power of Marks derived from Sothis herself. After betraying Sothis and unleashing chaos, Nemesis and his Elites were defeated by Seiros, who established the Church to safeguard Ansalon and ensure that the power of Marks would be used justly.<br><br>Over time, Marks became deeply intertwined with Ansalon’s noble houses. The ability to pass on Marks through bloodlines created an aristocratic society where noble families were distinguished by their possession of these powerful emblems. Marks granted not only physical and magical abilities but also significant social status and influence.<br>Noble families often arranged marriages to preserve and propagate their Marks, ensuring that their descendants would inherit these coveted powers. This led to a rigid class structure, where those without Marks, known as commoners, were often marginalized and excluded from positions of power.<br><br>The Church of Seiros played a central role in the study and regulation of Marks. Garreg Mach Monastery, the headquarters of the Church, housed extensive archives and scholars dedicated to understanding Marks and their origins. The Church’s influence ensured that Marks were revered as divine blessings, and it maintained strict control over Mark Stones, the physical manifestations of Marks.<br>Research into Marks was furthered by prominent scholars such as Saint Macuil, one of the Four Saints of the Church, who contributed significantly to the understanding of Marks and their applications. Despite the Church’s efforts to regulate Mark knowledge, some individuals and factions pursued secret research, seeking to harness the power of Marks for their own ends.<br><br>Throughout Ansalon’s history, the power of Marks has been a double-edged sword. While they granted incredible abilities to their bearers, they also fueled conflicts and power struggles. Noble houses often clashed over the possession and inheritance of Marks, leading to wars and rivalries that shaped the continent’s political landscape.<br>The Tragedy of Tarnis, a significant event in recent history, highlighted the destructive potential of Marks. The assassination of King Lambert of Solamnia and many of his retainers, allegedly due to a plot involving Mark bearers, plunged the Holy Kingdom of Solamnia into turmoil and had lasting repercussions on its young prince, Dimitri.<br><br>In the contemporary era of Ansalon, the significance of Marks came under scrutiny, particularly with the rise of Edelgard von Hresvelg. As the heir to the Abanasinian Empire and a bearer of the Mark of Seiros, Edelgard harbored a deep resentment towards the societal structures that Marks perpetuated. Her experiences and the secrets she uncovered led her to challenge the Church’s teachings and the nobility’s reliance on Marks.<br>Edelgard’s campaign aimed to dismantle the power of Marks and create a society where individuals were valued for their abilities and merits rather than their lineage. This radical vision sparked the War of the Eagle and Lion, a continent-wide conflict that sought to reshape Ansalon’s future.<br>]]></description><link>the-history-of-the-marks.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">The History of the Marks.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 02:31:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="pictures/marks/pasted-image-20240721172740.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="pictures/marks/pasted-image-20240721172740.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>