<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Dragonlance]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/</link><image><url>https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Dragonlance</title><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/</link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 21:04:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 21:04:18 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[54. August 23rd, 2025 The Greatest City In The Abyss]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>Heading West from the docks, Krynn's Vanguard entered a forest much similar to the ones they're used to on Krynn. Traveling through they found a trail off to the side and they trecked over to follow it. It was fairly well traveled as the ground cover had been crushed and died. The path was also recessed compared to the rest of the ground. While not well-planned, the path was wide enough for horses, carriages, and merchants to carry their wares through. Although it was fairly quiet as there were no other travelers in sight.<br>Breaking out of the forest into an open field was a city in a valley. Finally a source of civilization, hopefully it would provide some reprieve from the elements of The Abyss.<br>Upon reaching the city, the party met a greeter known as Overseer Anelith. Overseer Anelith tried to dissuade the party from seeking out The Gaping Maw. After all, they're in Bastagaal, 'The Greatest City in The Abyss'...why leave? Besides, Overseer Anelith said "We are safe now."<br>Exploring the city a bit, Krynn's Vanguard saw all sorts of people among the citizens of The Abyss. From humans to teiflings, tieflings to gungs, grungs to kobolds, and everything in between. The General Store was a point of interest as it only had half-walls and no attendants. One of the merchants showed the party that the store had some sort of magic around it where you picked up what you wanted, and once you left, it took the proper amount of gold from you. And if you returned the item in the condition it left the store as, you got your gold back. It was pretty cool. The conversation ended with the merchant saying "We are safe now."<br>One vendor in the city was a fashion designer who took a comission from Bob for a shirt that they would need a few days to make. Answering some questions, the party found that they had sold a fancy dress not that long ago of all sorts of colors designed like scales to a lady in black armor. Obviously Takhisis. So Takhisis was here for real, and seemingly beating the party to their destination. This merchant repeated the same phrase "We are safe now."<br>Exploring the library, The party found Illithid working in the library. The Illithid mentioned that they had no desire to comsume anyone's brains because, as the librarian said, "We are safe now."<br>Investigating further, Armantaro was pulled into a room by some sort of hand when he investigated a corner that seemed to have some odd magic about it. Here, he met an Illithid who seemed to be immune to 'The Will.' Some sort of cult leader that the party had heard about from other citizens of Bastagaal. This Illithid, known only as 'The Whisperer' mentioned that they had some of their commrades held captive by 'The Will', who was revealed to be Malgorzeth, The Lord of Chains. Seeking the party's help, he led them to a passage leading to The Obedience Engine. He also fixed Orion's bent Warhammer that was effective against fiends.<br>Venturing into The Obedience Engine, at least they thought. In a wide open room, they found floating platforms, connected by chains that had lighthing running throughout them. Once they got on a platform. Seven of creatures jumped out, ambushing them. Combat ensued and was giving Krynn's Vanguard a run for their money. How will they get out of this one?]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/session-notes/54.-august-23rd,-2025-the-greatest-city-in-the-abyss.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/54. August 23rd, 2025 The Greatest City In The Abyss.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:26:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[55. September 6th, 2025 Malgorzeth The Lord of Chains]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>Fighting the warriors and constructs that assumedly fought for Malgorzeth, Krynn's Vanguard was quickly expending their resources and needed a way out. Luckily, Armantaro saw a flash of light well above them and teleported up to investigate. He found a ledge and brought the rest of the party up in the next couple of rounds, escaping the fight.<br>on the platform, was a set of frosted sliding glass doors. Orla found a number of the same sets of doors before coming upon 5 sets of doors. The ones she came through, one set to the left, a set to the right, a set straight ahead, and a set above her with a spiraling staircase on either side.<br>Relaying this to the party, they debated which way to go, and decided to have Orion's spectral dragon investigate. They found 3 very similar rooms. The left room had 6 figures in grey cloaks with their heads down. At the back of the room was a sort of altar with a hole in the middle. Floating about a foot and a half off the ground was a blue crystal that was spinning at about 3-4 rotations per minute. The right had the same, but a yellow crystal. The room above them was the same, but was three rooms put together with 3 red crystals. The room ahead of them had chains hanging from the ceiling larger than they'd ever seen, each link bigger than the ship they used to cross Zebiom's Deep. And a massive figure with glowing red eyes, clawed hands and spiked armor standing about 50 feet tall. Completely still, not even a rising chest indicating life. The figures in the room were much the same.<br>Going through the rooms, Krynn's Vanguard found that they could destroy the crystals by hitting them with their weapons. This caused the figures to disappear, leaving their cloaks behind. No belongings were in the cloaks. Specifically Orion and Kyan were able to do this. <br>After destroying all the crystals., they went to confront Malgorzeth, but they found nothing had changed. Before just leaving and heading back, the party went back into one of the rooms and found the crystals and figures had returned. Krynn's Vanguard deduced that they needed to destroy all the crystals at the same time. Armantaro coordinated. <br>After returning to Malgorzeth's chamber, Armantaro and Kyan stepped forward before Armantaro was ambushed with chains out of nowhere. During the ensuing fight, Krynn's Vanguard was heavily handicapped being restrained, and having their attacks reduced in power for most of the fight. Armantaro somehow managed to land a heavy blow with Blade of Disaster and did a solid number to Malgorzeth that eventually was the deciding factor to defeating the Lord of Chains. With the fight over, what would happen now. Would The Whisperer still be at least neutral if not an ally? DId the Illithid regain their hunger for intellect? What would happen to Bastagaal? Was it still a safe place for those people to be? Only time would tell.]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/session-notes/55.-september-6th,-2025-malgorzeth-the-lord-of-chains.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/55. September 6th, 2025 Malgorzeth The Lord of Chains.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 21:04:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Session Notes]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br>]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/session-notes/session-notes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/Session Notes.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 19:47:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[East Road]]></title><description/></item></channel></rss>