<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Dragonlance]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/</link><image><url>https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Dragonlance</title><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/</link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 21:35:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 21:35:00 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[Session Notes]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br>]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/session-notes/session-notes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/Session Notes.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 22:01:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Welcome to Dragonlance]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>This website is a resource and reference for both the DM and players in the continuation of Dragonlance: Shadow of the Dragon Queen campaign that takes place every Saturday at 6PM at Duke City Games (with exceptions for extenuating circumstances).<br><br>The world has ended, and it’s ending again.<br>Three hundred years ago, the Cataclysm brought ruin to the world of Krynn. In a single day, an age of wonders came to an end. Countless innocents died, the face of the world was reshaped, and the gods themselves faded into legend. Through ages of struggle, the peoples of Krynn survived, but the world isn’t what it was. Those nations that remain linger in the shadows of their ancestors’ wonders. Only slowly have they begun to push back centuries of darkness and rediscover how the world has changed.<br>Then came the Dragon Armies, legions of soldiers devoted to the wicked god Takhisis the Dragon Queen, and the world faces ruin once more. The War of the Lance has begun, and in a conflict between gods and dragons, a wounded world hangs in the balance.<br><br>As a last effort to avoid mass destruction, the gods sent the Thirteen Warnings, a series of signs meant to deter the kingpriest. Trees wept blood, fires raged unnaturally, and cyclones struck the gleaming Temple of the Kingpriest. The gods also warned a few chosen mortals, reasoning that if any of them reached Istar and prevented the ritual, the world might not be beyond redemption. But the messengers failed—the kingpriest and his followers dismissed the warnings as the work of evil and continued on their path. As the hour of the kingpriest’s ritual to attain godhood arrived, the gods whisked away their most devout followers and unleashed punishment on all who remained.<br>A mountain of fire fell from the sky, destroying Istar. The Blood Sea—a new ocean that split eastern Ansalon—consumed the empire. Coastlines shifted all over the world, sundering nations, drowning whole regions, and stranding ports miles from the sea. Though some lands escaped the worst of the destruction, none were spared divine wrath.<br>The gods and their blessings then faded from the world, and in time, even their names were all but forgotten.<br><br>The Cataclysm ushered in a period of chaos. During the next three centuries, known as the Time of Darkness, cultures and ecologies were radically altered, causing famine, plague, and mass migrations. The Knights of Solamnia, the champions who might’ve kept Ansalon united, were distrusted as former allies of Istar and persecuted across the continent, even in Solamnia.<br>The elven nations shut their borders. The dwarves of Thorbardin withdrew to their deep tunnels, refusing entrance to refugees from the surface. Many societies turned on one another or fell to disease and war. Nations of hobgoblins and ogres spread, capitalizing on humanity’s decline and claiming whole regions. Much that survived the Cataclysm was lost in darkness.<br>At length, the worst effects of the disaster waned. Though many elves and mountain dwarves remained reclusive, other cultures tentatively rebuilt. Explorers ventured forth to map the drastically altered continent. Societies reestablished bonds of trade that united and diversified them.<br>As the civilizations of Krynn rebuilt, and new societies arose, the world learned to live with a jarring truth: the gods were truly gone. Religion on Krynn was altered forever. True clerics, who once worked miracles on behalf of their gods, had vanished. While some people remained devout, many others turned to false religions in search of answers and comfort. Some of these new faiths were founded by charlatans, others by zealots. Some claimed the names of the gods, others dismissed them entirely. In this radically changed world bereft of immortal insight, truth became subject to conjecture, even among Krynn’s most dedicated scholars.<br><br>Even as Ansalon healed, a new threat grew. The Dragon Queen Takhisis—known as Tiamat on other worlds—was banished from Krynn over a thousand years ago. Since then, she had waited patiently, plotting her return. Unbeknownst to the other gods, she planted a piece of the kingpriest’s ruined temple at Neraka—hidden in the volcanic Taman Busuk region. There it grew into a baleful shadow of Istar’s greatest edifice. Though this allowed the Dragon Queen to influence the world through a portal opened there, a fragment of the temple’s foundation stone was missing, preventing her from fully returning to the world. She called on the evil dragons who served her, long withdrawn from the world, and began once more to plot the conquest of Krynn.<br>Chromatic dragons, acting on their god’s orders, stole the eggs of good metallic dragons. The metallic dragons reluctantly pledged to not interfere in the coming war in exchange for the promised safety of their abducted broods.<br>But the Dragon Queen’s servants secretly broke their promises. Takhisis taught her followers to corrupt the stolen eggs into monstrous warriors known as draconians, gambling that draconian armies will conquer Ansalon by the time the metallic dragons learn of this betrayal.<br>Unrivaled by gods or dragons, the Dragon Queen unleashes her forces upon a shattered world. In their god’s name, these Dragon Armies begin their conquest of Krynn.<br><br>The Dragon Queen’s forces are organized into five Dragon Armies. Draconians fill the ranks of each, though the armies’ numbers also include humans, goblins, hobgoblins, ogres, and others who seek wealth and a return to pre-Cataclysm glories. Each Dragon Army is supported by chromatic dragons and their smaller kin, such as dragonnels and wyverns. These winged terrors provide a staggering advantage not seen on battlefields for over a thousand years.<br>The Dragon Queen has elevated her five most cunning and devout followers to the rank of dragon highlord, each commanding one of her armies. The highlords all report to Takhisis’s champion, Duulket Ariakas, but there is no shortage of treachery between—and within—the Dragon Armies. The Dragon Queen encourages these conflicts, trusting them to bring the most ruthless and capable leaders to prominence.<br>The Red Dragon Army—the first, largest, and most powerful of Takhisis’s forces—is commanded by the fanatical Dragon Highlord Verminaard, but he has temporarily given control of many of its troops to his acolyte, Dragon Highmaster Kansaldi Fire-Eyes, tasking her with spearheading a daring attack on Solamnia. Meanwhile, Verminaard’s force follows whispers from the Dragon Queen into the southern lands of Abanasinia.<br>The ambitious Highlord Kitiara Uth Matar commands the Blue Dragon Army. Second in power among the Dragon Queen’s forces, the Blue Dragon Army prepares to join the Red Dragon Army’s multipronged invasion of Solamnia. The Green Dragon Army recently came under the command of Salah-Khan, a Khur leader who united the region’s nomads under Dragon Army rule. The half-ogre Lucien of Takar commands the Black Dragon Army, whose focused force supports the other armies and occupies the lands they conquer, including Nordmaar and Goodlund. Finally, the small White Dragon Army is led by Highlord Feal-Thas, a Silvanesti elf and black-robed member of the Mages of High Sorcery.<br><br><br>The first true military test of the Dragon Armies was the Red and Green Dragon Armies’ successful invasion of the unprepared realm of Nordmaar. This victory convinced many neutral bands of hobgoblins and ogres in the Taman Busuk region to align with the Dragon Armies, though many holdouts remain.<br><br>The Green Dragon Army was dispatched to the steppes of Khur to subdue the tribes there. Rather than fight a protracted campaign, Ariakas allowed the cunning Khur leader Salah-Khan to defeat the Green Dragon Army’s original highlord in battle, then offered to make Salah-Khan highlord in his place. In exchange for control over Khur and the surrounding lands, Salah-Khan accepted and pledged his people to Takhisis, adding to the Dragon Armies’ ranks. Few can say whether he did so to further his own ambitions or to spare Khur a long, bloody conflict, but many Khur view Salah-Khan as a traitor to his people and fiercely resist the Green Dragon Army’s occupation.<br><br>Without substantial military resistance, Balifor and the Goodlund Peninsula fell to the Black and White Dragon Armies. Though the land’s residents are largely resigned to the Black Dragon Army’s ongoing occupation, the kender of Kendermore lead the region’s resistance, waging a guerrilla war against the occupiers.<br><br>The Red and Blue Dragon Armies attacked the elven nation of Silvanesti. The elves mounted a stiff resistance, and the siege stretched on in a brutal campaign.<br>
After a year of fighting, the Silvanesti elves evacuated from their ancestral home and sailed for Southern Ergoth.<br><br>With virtually all of eastern Ansalon under their control, the Dragon Armies have spent much of the last year regrouping and consolidating their power. The Blue and Red Dragon Armies have returned to the Taman Busuk region, tasked with preparing to invade Solamnia. The White Dragon Army has ventured south to conquer Icereach, where its white dragons can fight effectively in its frozen lands. The Green and Black Dragon Armies focus on their occupied lands abroad.<br>In Neraka, zealots and black-robed mages devise magical plans to empower Dragon Army forces. One such plot, involving the ruins of an Istarian city, captures the imagination of Dragon Highlord Verminaard. He tasks his devotee, Kansaldi Fire-Eyes, with claiming a devastating new weapon for the Dragon Armies.<br><br><a class="internal-link" data-href="Ansalon-Map.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/ansalon-map.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Ansalon-Map</a><br>
<a data-href="Session Notes" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/session-notes/session-notes.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Session Notes</a><br><br><br><a class="internal-link" data-href="The Abanasinian Empire.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/the-abanasinian-empire.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Abanasinian Empire</a><br>
<a class="internal-link" data-href="The Holy Kingdom of Solamnia.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/the-holy-kingdom-of-solamnia.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Holy Kingdom of Solamnia</a><br>
<a class="internal-link" data-href="The Qualinesti Alliance.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/the-qualinesti-alliance.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Qualinesti Alliance</a><br>
<a class="internal-link" data-href="Church of Seiros" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/church-of-seiros.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Church of Seiros</a><br>
<a class="internal-link" data-href="The History of the Marks.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/the-history-of-the-marks.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The History of the Marks</a><br>
<a data-href="The Abyssal Concord of Utter Chaos" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/the-abyssal-concord-of-utter-chaos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Abyssal Concord of Utter Chaos</a><br>
<a data-href="Those Who Slither in the Dark" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/those-who-slither-in-the-dark.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Those Who Slither in the Dark</a><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br>]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/dragonlance-home.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Dragonlance - Home.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 21:32:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>