<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Dragonlance]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/</link><image><url>https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Dragonlance</title><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/</link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 22:01:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 22:01:12 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator></dc:creator><item><title><![CDATA[60. November 22nd, 2025 The Prince of Demons]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>It had been a long and arduous journey through The Abyss, but it was finally here, the last hurdle before grabbing another piece of The Crest of the Daughters of Paladine, and getting out of the Abyss, if not unharmed, at least alive. The only thing standing before them, was The Prince of Demons himself, The Demogorgon.<br>The fight itself was longer than the journey to get there itself, many times it seemed that Krynn's Vanguard would be another one of the stories of those who went to the Abyss, never to return. Alas, Krynn's Vanguard prevailed, defeating the Demogorgon, and claiming the second to last piece of The Crest of the Daughters of Paladine, The shard of Querrasian, the Copper Daughter of Paladine.<br>After defeating The Prince of Demons, Krynn's Vanguard was teleported back to Dargaard Keep, where they would plan their next move.]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/session-notes/60.-november-22nd,-2025-the-prince-of-demons.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/60. November 22nd, 2025 The Prince of Demons.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 21:07:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[61. December 13th, 2025 Return to Dargaard]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>Awakening, Krynn's Vanguard found themselves back in Dargaard Keep. After planning a bit, they decided to meet with Marena Stonereed, the dwarven ledgerkeeper they met and saved in Thorbardin.<br>
Marena Stonereed clears her throat once, adjusts the iron clasp on her ledger, and plants both hands flat upon the table.
“Right. You’re back, and the world hasn’t ended yet. That’s a good start.”
She flips open the ledger—its pages thick, worn, and meticulous.
“Six months. That’s how long you were gone. Long enough for a fortress to either fall apart or find its feet.” 
A faint, satisfied grunt. 
“Dargaard found its feet.”
She taps the page.
“The Keep is functional. Not pretty everywhere, not finished anywhere, but sound. The inner halls are sealed against the weather. Roof’s holding. Towers are braced. I left the old scars where they didn’t threaten collapse—folk remember what a place has survived better when they can see it.”
She gestures vaguely toward the walls.“
The dead knights you left us—the Foresworn—have made the place… efficient. No patrol schedules needed. No wages. No desertions. They manifest when something threatens the Keep or the lands, and not before. Whatever binds them, it’s stable.”
A pause.
“I’ve stopped asking questions about that.”
She turns a page.
“The Vogler folk took to the land quicker than expected. Turns out people who’ve lost everything work hard when given ground that’s theirs. Fields are laid, rotation’s in place, irrigation’s drawing from old keep runoff and new channels. We’ve got grain enough for winter and surplus besides.”
She glances up at you.
“No one’s starving. That matters.”
Another page.
“We rebuilt the south granary and raised two more storehouses. A mill’s running near the old road. Blacksmith’s shop’s operational—tools, nails, plowshares, weapons if needed. Trade caravans stop here now. Not because they’re brave—because the roads are safe.”
Her mouth twitches.
“Nothing that scouts Dargaard comes back to tell tales.”
She moves on without dwelling.
“Income’s steady. Taxes are fair. Paid in coin, grain, or labor—folk choose. Excess goes back into roads, roofs, and people who know what they’re doing. I’ve hired masons, carpenters, teamsters. No fools, no thieves.”
She raps the ledger once, sharply.“
Anyone who tried skimming learned better. Quietly.”
She flips again.
“The keep’s old crypt levels are sealed and warded. Access limited to you and the Foresworn. The rest of us don’t go down there. We don’t need to.”
A shorter pause. Colder.
“Some doors stay shut for good reasons.”
She turns another page—this one marked with a small, stamped sigil of a sword and crown.
"Oh. And the militia.”
She folds her arms.
“The Foresworn didn’t care for leaving the defense of the lands to chance. Turns out they remember more than how to haunt corridors.”
Her tone is measured now. Respectful.“
They were Knights of Solamnia once. That shows.”
She nods toward the courtyard outside.
“They drilled the folk. Properly. Shield walls. Rotations. Formations that hold when fear sets in. Not fancy—effective. They taught discipline before swordplay. When to stand. When to fall back. When to protect someone who can’t protect themselves.”
A pause.
“They didn’t shout. Didn’t threaten. They stood there in silence until everyone else learned to do the same.”She flips the page.“The militia isn’t an army. But they’re trained. They know Solamnic calls and signals. They can hold a line long enough for help to arrive—or die buying time.”
She meets your eyes again.“
And the dead knights took no credit. No titles. No loyalty oaths.”
Just a hint of something like admiration.
“They told the folk they were not teaching them to win wars.”
“They were teaching them how not to break.”
Marena closes the ledger.
“You didn’t leave us a treasure hoard. You left us a ruin and a name people were afraid of.”
She meets each of your eyes in turn.
“You came back to a domain.”
A nod, crisp and final.
“That’s all I have for you. If you’re planning a war—and everyone assumes you are—this place can support it.”
She allows herself one small, ironclad smile.
“And if the world survives… it’ll last after you’re gone.”
<br>With that, Krynn's Vanguard decided to check in with a few of their allies to see what info they had. Without much info on the Dragon Isles besides knowing they are north of Ansalon, Krynn's Vanguard only got info from <a data-href="Edelgard Von Hresvelg" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/npcs/the-black-eagles/edelgard-von-hresvelg.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Edelgard Von Hresvelg</a> that they were preparing a strike on the Green Dragon Army who was stationed in <a class="internal-link" data-href="Southern Ergoth Locations.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/locations/southern-ergoth/southern-ergoth-locations.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Southern Ergoth</a> seemingly planning their own attack.<br>With the Blue and Red Dragon Arnies holding positions in <a class="internal-link" data-href="Locations/Plains of Dust/Plains of Dust Locations.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/locations/plains-of-dust/plains-of-dust-locations.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Plains of Dust</a> and Taman Busuk, and the Black Dragon Army across <a class="internal-link" data-href="Locations/Khur/Khur Locations.md" href="https://krynns-vanguard.com/locations/khur/khur-locations.html" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Khur</a> and Kendermore, it looked as if the Green Dragon Army gained a foothold in Qualnesti, it would culminate in an attack from the East and South, pushing Solamnia towards their coasts, which they were not prepared to flee from.<br>The next steps were to plan their moves, and coordinate with the Imperial Army once more to have a path to The Green Dragon Army.]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/session-notes/61.-december-13th,-2025-return-to-dargaard.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/61. December 13th, 2025 Return to Dargaard.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 22:00:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Session Notes]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br>]]></description><link>https://krynns-vanguard.com/session-notes/session-notes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Session Notes/Session Notes.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 22:01:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>